二次运球
Double dribble.
有吗? 嫌我长得黑吧?
Why, because I'm black?
哼 我就知道
Yeah, that's what I thought.
我?
Me?
还剩10秒了 再来一球啊
Ten seconds left. We need a basket.
1978年天主教青年组织 城市篮球决赛
进一个 进一个
Play one. Play one.
Kurt Kurt  Kurt 这里
Kurt, Kurt, Kurt. Here.
送进去
Get in.
送进去!
Bring it in!
打篮板 Lenny
Bank's open, Lenny.
好的 好的!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
太好了
Yeah.
好球
Bank's open.
他踩线了
His foot was on the line.
首先 我要感谢Earnshaw一家
First off, I'd like to thank the Earnshaw family...
把这美丽的湖畔别墅借给我们 庆祝胜利
...for lending us their beautiful lake house to help us celebrate our victory.
Ferdinando 五虎!
Yeah, the Ferdinando Five.
他们最棒了
They're dynamite.
你喝多了 爸爸
You're drunk, Dad.
是嘛
Yeah.
我们是为孩子们庆祝 不是你
Hey. We're here to celebrate the kids' shots, not your shots.
不管怎样 我得说说孩子们下午的比赛
Anyway, I wanna talk about what you kids did this afternoon.
知道吗 你们的表现令我非常满意
You know, you played the game just like I always ask you to.
因为你们全力以赴的比赛
You left everything you had out there on that court.
所以当终场哨音响起的时候...
So that when the final buzzer went off...
冠军就属于你们了
...you were champions.
现在 我要你们答应我
Now, I want you to promise me something.
我要你们像今天的比赛一样 去追求你们的生活
I want you to play life just like you played that game today.
这样在人生的终场哨音响起之时
So when that final buzzer of life goes off...
你们将心安无憾
...you'll have no regrets.
敬教练
Here's to coach.
你们是我的第一支冠军队
You're my first champions. My first champions.
你们要团结
Stick together.
- 死期到了 - 不要
- Time to die. - No.
30年后 加州贝弗利山庄
绝杀
Murder.
我可是好莱坞最大牌经纪人 而你敢把我惹毛了
I am the biggest agent in Hollywood and you just pissed me off.
我要让布拉德皮特退出你的电影
And now I'll pull Brad Pitt from your movie.
还有茱莉亚罗伯茨 我才不管 Sandy
I'll pull Julia Roberts from your movie. I don't care, Sandy.
这才对 你最好让步
That's right, you better back down.
谢谢
Thank you.
独立日快乐 好了 我也爱你
Have a good Fourth of July. All right, love you too.
嘿 孩子们
What's up, boys? Hey.
Greggie Keithie
Greggie, Keithie.
你们有没玩过 滑坡与梯子?
You guys ever hear of a game called Chutes and Ladders?
非常棒的游戏
Pretty awesome game.
我小时候就玩这个
I used to play it when I was a kid.
你会拿到一个转盘
Okay, what it is, is they give you a spinner.
如果转到梯子 你就可以爬上去
And you spin. If you land on a ladder, you get to climb up the ladder.
如果转到滑梯 你就得滑下来重头开始
If you land on a chute, you slide down the chute and start over again.
那又怎样? 赢了奖励个小胸罩?
Yeah, and what happens? The winner gets a training bra?
爸 那游戏听起来逊毙了
Yeah, Dad, that game sounds like it sucks.
告诉你们 这游戏非常好玩
I'm telling you, this was the greatest game.
我和兄弟们会在冬天
Me and my buddies would play it.
跑到地下室 倒杯热可可 玩上一整天
We'd go down in the basement, drink hot chocolate.
我现在可顾不上热可可
I wouldn't mind a hot chocolate right now.
Rita
Hey, Rita.
Rita.
伙计 你得给她发信息 她在洗衣服
Dude, you gotta text her. She's doing laundry.
对了 爸 我们昨天去了斯皮尔伯格家
Hey, Dad, we were at the Spielbergs' house yesterday.
他家有台150英寸的电视 我们能不能也买一台?
They have a 150-inch TV. Can we get one of those?
等你导演了"ET"我就给你买
When you direct E. T. I'll get you one of those.
- 求你放了我 - 这游戏到底要干什么?
- Beg for mercy. - What is the object here? I don't get it.
跑游轮上 用链锯砍其他人的头?
You're on a cruise ship and you chop people's heads off with a chain saw?
你还可以淹死他们
Oh, and you can drown them.
还能淹死他们 我明白了
Oh, you can drown them. Now I get it.
老奶奶坠船了 (加200分)
Granny overboard.
有人能接下电话吗?
Can somebody answer the phone?
也许我也该弄点甘菊润润嗓子
Maybe I should get some chamomile for my throat too.
别给保姆发短信了 你不觉得一个孩子
Stop texting the nanny. You know how gross that is...
给保姆发短信很恶心吗? 自己去走廊叫
...for a kid to text his nanny? Just go down the hallway.
为什么? 你给其他人也发短信的
Why? You text everybody.
我给人发短信是为了工作 才能挣钱付你们的短信费
I text people for my job so I can make money to pay for your texting.
- 孩子们 你们要的我都拿来了 - 谁的电话 Rita?
- Okay, I got everything for you, boys. - Who was that on the phone, Rita?
对不起Feder先生 我不知道 Becky接的
I'm sorry, Mr. Feder, I don't know. Becky answered.
- 好了 谢谢你做的 - 天哪 Rita
- Okay, okay. Thanks for making that. - Oh, my God, Rita.
这不是Godiva的 你是在下毒吗? (全球最精致的手工巧克力公司)
This isn't Godiva. What are you, trying to poison me?
天哪 你们还是发短信吧
Good Lord, go back to texting.
我可不想听你们大吼大叫了
I don't ever wanna hear that out loud again.
外面什么情况?
What the heck's going on out here?
天哪
Oh, my God.
我不是故意的 这是意外
I didn't mean to. It was an accident.
别管它 你没事吧? 你在干什么啊?
I don't care. Are you all right? What the heck were you doing?
我在试着用导舟
I was trying to use the Navy.
导舟? 什么导舟啊?
The Navy? What's the Navy?
车里的导舟 可以问他问题
The Navy in the car to ask it a question.
你说的是导航仪 笨蛋
You mean the navigation system, idiot.
- Keithie 别说了 - 有人给你打电话
- Keithie, relax. - Some man called.
他说你的朋友 哨音教练去天堂了
He said your friend, Coach Buzzer, went to heaven.
我在用导舟帮你找天堂
I was trying to find heaven for you on the Navy station...
这样你就可以去看他了
...so you could go visit him.
你那朋友是谁啊 爸爸?
Who's your friend, Dad?
哨音教练是爸爸生命中 非常特别的一个人
Coach Buzzer was someone very special in Daddy's life.
太糟糕了
It's terrible.
和他们进屋去喝点热可可吧
Okay, go drink some hot chocolate with these guys.
你真没事吧?
You sure you're okay?
好 亲爱的
Okay, sweetie.
你洒到你弟弟了
You're splashing your brother.
Eric 亲爱的 你妈妈的电话
Eric, hon? It's your mom.
天哪 Eric 你没事吧?
Oh, my God. Eric. Are you all right?
Donna
Donna.
天哪 Bean 呆在小鸭子上
Oh, my God, Bean. Bean, stay on the duck.
发生什么了?
Stay on the duck. What is happening?
天哪 亲爱的
Oh, hon.
你好 妈妈
Hello, Mommy.
- 你好 - 你好 妈妈
- Hey. - Hey, Mom.
你好 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
好的 过去再说
Well, I'll see you there. All right.
出了什么事?
Hey, is something wrong?
没事的 我等下和你说
Yeah, it'll be all right. I'll talk to you about it later.
Hey, hey.
我做了意大利南瓜饭
I made the pumpkin risotto that we saw...
和Rachael Ray 夏季特别节目上的一样噢
...on Rachael Ray's "Seasons of Summer" special.
Rachael Ray是美国电视烹饪女王
- 烂透了 妈妈 - 味道就像被撞死的动物
- It's awful, Mom. - It tastes like roadkill.
Deanne 你听到他们怎么 对我说话的吗?
Deanne, do you hear how they talk to me? Do you hear how...?
你得说说他们
You gotta say something.
好了 孩子们 你们爸爸要打扫房子
All right, kids. Now, you know your father works very hard...
还要为我们做吃的 非常辛苦
...at keeping this house clean and putting meals on the table for us.
而你们呢?
Hello?
除此之外
Besides...
我买了个披萨
...I brought us a pizza.
知道吗? 好吧
You know what? Fine.
吃你们披萨 吃你们披萨
Have your pizza. Have your pizza.
你们伤了我的心
You broke my heart.
他每个月的那时候又来了
Looks like it's his time of the month again.
天哪 那真痛苦啊 伙计
God, that's rough, buddy.
谁在筹备葬礼?
Who's making the funeral arrangements?
他的侄女? 她肯定心力交瘁了
Oh, his niece? She must be devastated.
她还是那么性感吗?
Hey, is she still hot, do you know?
别把我惹火了 Marcus
Don't make me lose my temper, Marcus.
什么?
What?
如果我最后没能出席葬礼
Hey, if I don't make it to the funeral...
告诉警察是Applebee餐厅的Arlene干的
...tell the police it was Arlene from Applebee's.
谢谢你通知我
No, thanks for calling me.
到时候见
And I'll see you there.
再见
Bye.
教练去世了
The coach is dead.
葬礼在星期五
His funeral is this Friday.
我恐怕一个人扛不住
I don't think I can handle this alone.
你能陪我一起去吗?
Can you come with me?
当然可以
Of course.
我会推迟白内障手术的
I'll postpone my cataract surgery.
你是我的女神
You are my special lady.
现在我要带你进入一个 平静祥和的世界
Now I'm gonna transport you to a world of serene relaxation.
新英格兰
好了 伙计们 让我们表现的正常点
Okay, guys, let's try to act normal in there.
为什么不戴太阳镜了?
What's wrong with your sunglasses?
我可不想有机会让他们叫我
I don't want any reason for these guys to call me...
好莱坞!
Hollywood!
- 嘿 看看是谁啊 Kurt McKenzie - 嘿
- Hey. Look at that. Kurt McKenzie. - Hey.
- 还有McKenzie全家 - 你好
- And the whole McKenzie clan. - Come here, man.
- Deanne 你看起来不错 - 是嘛?
- Deanne, you look great. - I do?
我妻子在那儿 去打个招呼吧 孩子们好
My wife's over there. Go and say hi. Children.
你屁股又长大了
I see that ass is still growing.
我们多了个小Kardashian (美国性感人物)
Got a little Kardashian in there.
你快变成小号的Michael Vick了 如果他也够贪吃的话
Well, you've kind of turned into a little Michael Vick thing, if he was bulimic.
美国橄榄球星
你好 Roxanne
Hi, Roxanne.
还记得我吗 我参加过你的婚礼
I don't know if you remember me. I was at your wedding.
我就是整晚在桌子上跳舞的那个 我叫Deanne McKenzie
I was the one that was table dancing all night. Deanne McKenzie.
当然
Of course.
- Deanne 你好 - 见到你真好
- Deanne, hello. - Hi, good to see you.
你看上去容光焕发
Oh, my God, you're glowing.
怀孕了还这么漂亮
You look so beautiful with your pregnancy.
你他妈说什么呢?
What the hell are you talking about?
我开玩笑的
I'm just playing.
看你那表情 "怎么了?"
Oh, my God. You should see your face. You were like, "Huh?"
小小Lenny Feder
Little Lenny Feder.
Ronzoni妈妈又胖了?
Mama Ronzoni got big, huh?
看看这个大帅哥
Look at this handsome hunk of prosciutto.
这个大人物
And such a big success.
来给妈妈亲一下
Come on, give Mama a kiss.
能...? 能亲到脸颊吗?
Can I get a...? Can I get a cheek at all?
我亲到了 虽然眼睛被帽子戳了一下 不过没事
I got you, I got you. Poked in the eye by the hat, but I'm all right.
你女婿怎么了 据说变家庭煮夫了
How about your son-in-law here, I hear he's a house husband now.
我女儿每天拼死拼活赚钱付账单
My daughter's gotta bust her hump all day to pay the bills...
而那个蠢蛋却在家打扫卫生
...while dummy here stays home and cleans.
你凭什么这样说我
I don't know how you could talk to me like that...
你自己都是个头顶螺旋桨的傻子
...when you look like Idi Amin with a propeller on your head.
- 幸好他还能... - Roxanne 这是我母亲
- That's nice that he could... - Roxanne, this is my mother.
你好 Ronzoni妈妈 很高兴见到你 我是小Lenny的妻子
Hello, Mama Ronzoni, I'm so pleased to meet you. I'm Little Lenny's wife.
是个墨西哥大美女啊 真有你的 Lenny
What a spicy quesadilla you got yourself, Lenny.
是呀 她很赞的
Yeah, she tastes great.
我想也是
I bet.
我不是说过来这要关手机的吗 Greg?
Didn't I tell you to turn the phone off there, Greg?
但这是我的按摩理疗师
Yeah, but it's my massage therapist.
什么? 不 不行 不准打手机
What? No, no. No cell phones.
不能打手机? 那我走了哦
No cell phones? Then I'm out of here.
Higgie
Higgie.
谁准备好葬礼了?
Who's ready to get their funeral on?
抱歉 死亡让我变得很奇怪
I'm sorry, death makes me weird.
你好呀 McKenzie
What's up, McKenzie?
手真软 还在用Palmolive? (棕榄，1928年收购了高露洁)
You got those soft hands. Still using Palmolive?
最近怎样 Lenny?
Hey, what's up, Lenny?
兄弟 我以为你有在健身呢
Buddy, I thought you were gonna start working out.
- 什么意思? - 你发福了
- What does that mean? - You're fat.
没有
No. No.
嘿 有个好事我一直想问你
Hey, guys, this is good news. I always wanted to represent you.
你是Olsen Twins的老三吗? (美国著名美女姐妹艺人)
You're the third Olsen twin?
别闹了 这是你的孩子们吗?
Keep it down. Hey, so these are your kids?
那个女孩是谁? 不会是保姆吧?
And who's that girl? That's not a nanny, is it?
不 不 这是我们的一个中国朋友
No, no, this is a friend of ours from China.
是嘛 我也上那个网站
Oh, yeah. No, I've been on that website.
不 不不
No, no, no.
她是交换生... 我老婆带回来的
Like an exchange student that... My wife brought her into the house.
你老婆喜欢小妞啊 那太棒了
Oh, your wife's into chicks. Oh, that's nice.
好莱坞 他总是这么幸运
Hollywood. See, he always lucks out.
- 她只是个交换生 - 我一直以为...
- Just an exchange student. - I always thought...
伙计们
Hey, now.
Lamonsoff 混上凯迪拉克了?
Lamonsoff. Rolling up in a Caddy?
这就是我们的生活
That's how we do it.
看看你 长大了啊 现在用B罩杯啦?
And you, you've grown up on me, man. Are you a B-cup now?
耳朵长得不错 靠它们拿到橄榄球联盟套票的?
Hey, nice ears. You get the NFL package on those?
凯迪拉克真帅 你在卖草坪家具和毒品吗?
Nice Caddy. You selling lawn furniture and crack?
我可是Branchville草坪家具 的合伙人
Come on, I'm the co-owner of Branchville Lawn Furniture, man.
我现在是老板了
I'm the boss now, baby.
真不错 Eric
Oh, good for you, Eric.
- 很高兴能带你妈来了 - 这玩笑不错
- Glad you brought your mother. - Oh, that's a good one.
感觉像和老鹰握手 一会儿见
It's like shaking hands with an Eagle. I'll see you later.
天哪 那是唱诗班里的Caring主唱
Oh, my God. It's Captain Caring of the SS Melodrama.
他要大显身手了
Oh, he's gonna play this one big.
说"嘿"
Cue "Hey."
嘿
Hey.
- 气氛真伤感? - 我知道 我知道 很伤心
- Hell of a circumstance, huh? - I know, I know. It sucks.
见到你真好
Great to see you.
哨音在上面训练他的天堂之队去了
Well, the Buzzer's up there coaching heaven's team now.
- 是啊 - 有Wilt Pistol Pete Dr.J.
- That's true. - He's got Wilt, Pistol Pete, Dr. J.
3人均是NBA球星
Dr. J.还活着
Yeah, Dr. J's alive still.
- 反正像他那样的 - 是啊
- Well, those type of guys. - Yeah, yeah.
你看起来气色不错
You look good, though, man.
像是小矮人版的猫王
It's like if Elvis was an Oompa Loompa...
...he's right in front of me.
我不在葬礼上开玩笑 太失礼了
Well, I don't make jokes at funerals because it's disrespectful.
但如果这样能让你不那么伤心 我就不介意
But if that's part of your healing process, I'm cool with it.
你真好 谢谢
That's nice. Thanks.
你介意我用手指头插你么?
Are you cool with a finger in you?
Roxanne
Hey, Roxanne.
记得Rob吗 我总和你提起的? Rob?
Remember Rob, the guy I always tell you about? Rob?
当然
Of course.
19岁才进入青春期的那孩子?
The kid who didn't hit puberty till he was 19, right?
那是我们的秘密
That was our secret.
这位一定是你妈妈
And this must be your mother.
我妻子
My wife.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你好 我是Gloria
Hi. I'm Gloria.
很高兴见到你 你的衣着设计很漂亮
Oh, it's so nice to meet you. Your design line is so beautiful.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you, thank you.
- 我喜欢你的 围巾 - 谢谢你
- And I love your scarves. - Thank you.
她过会儿要用它把我捆起来
She'll be tying me up with those later.
他不是开玩笑
He's not kidding.
哦 恶心
Oh, grody.
你们舌头真长
Oh, those are long, long tongues.
我们里头见 里头见
We'll see you in there. See you in there.
你们好 那里吗? 是的
Hi, guys. Right over there? Yep.
坐这里 坐这里 我要去和Lenny问好
Sit right here, sit right here. I'm gonna go say hi to Lenny.
- 不 亲爱的 - 你好 Lenny
- No, honey. - Oh, hi. Lenny.
你好吗?
How you doing?
我听人说
I heard through a little bird...
你们租了Earnshaw湖畔别墅
...that you guys rented the Earnshaw lake house for us...
给大家过周末
...for the entire weekend.
这就好像梦想成真
That's like a dream come true for us.
我们租整个周末 是因为...
We had to rent it for the whole weekend be...
但我们不会一直呆在那里 因为我们明天得去米兰
We don't get to stay the whole weekend. We have to go to Milan.
Roxanne有个时装秀
For Roxanne's fashion show.
天哪 多可惜啊
Oh, my God, that's a shame.
但你们在米兰会玩的很开心的
Oh, but you're gonna have so much fun in Milan.
詹妮弗・洛佩兹和马克・安东尼 去年就在那渡假的
You know, J Lo and Marc Anthony vacationed there last year.
就在Lake Como的那条街上 乔治・克鲁尼的别墅旁边
It's up the street from Lake Como, where George Clooney has a villa.
米兰著名的度假胜地
我八卦杂志看太多啦
I read too many of those magazines.
- 不 - 来吧 抱歉
- No. - Come on. I'm sorry.
- 他讨厌我谈论这个 - 我们只是...
- He hates when I talk about this. - We'll just...
我们回去了 真不好意思 是不是?
We are backing away. Ashamed, right?
对了 汤姆・克鲁斯也在那儿结婚的
Oh, and Tom Cruise got married there too.
- 谢谢你告诉我 - 什么?
- Thanks for letting me know. - What?
我不明白你为什么必须租整个周末
Well, I don't understand why you had to rent it for a whole weekend.
因为是假期 单独一晚人家不租给你
Because it's a holiday. They won't rent it to you for one night.
那当你困在沉闷的米兰时 你朋友们可以狂欢了
So your friends are partying all weekend while you're stuck in Milan.
- 是啊 - 你真是贴心啊
- Yeah. - That was nice of you.
应该说我们俩很贴心 也是你的钱吧?
It was nice of us. It's your money too, isn't it?
是啊 是你的钱 也是他的 还是我的
Yeah, it's your money, it's his money, it's my money.
我们把钱混一起然后分了吧
Let's put all our cash in a pile and split it.
不错的帽子 给房间里带来生气
That's a nice hat, it brings out the death in the room.
抱歉 我很紧张 葬礼搞得我怪怪的
I'm sorry, I'm nervous. And it's a funeral, I get weird.
他在那儿 好莱坞
There he is, Joe Hollywood.
大牌经纪人
Mr. Big Shot Agent.
你觉得他能代表Hulk Hogan吗? (美国八、九十年代的摔角偶像)
You think he represents Hulk Hogan?
不可能
No way.
那他也没那么大牌吧?
Then he ain't that big, is he?
顺便说下 有人问的话就说Rita是个交换生
By the way, if anyone asks, Rita is an exchange student.
Andre
Andre.
我想我坐在你的计算器上了
I think I just sat on your adding machine.
现在我知道鱼缸是怎么回事了
Now I know what happened to the fish tank.
Robert教练 人称哨音Ferdinando
Coach Robert "The Buzzer" Ferdinando...
是一个守护者
...was a caretaker by profession.
这是多么美好的一个词 来总结他毕生的贡献
What a wonderful word to describe his devotion to his fellow man.
他全力以赴的去守护
He truly took care.
当Robert知道他时日不多时
When Robert knew that his time was short...
他告诉我 他想让一个人
...he told me there was one specific man he wanted...
说几句话 来悼念他
...to say a few words to memorialize him.
请Lenny Feder上台吧
So I'd like to ask Lenny Feder to come up now.
抱歉 我完全没有准备
I'm sorry, I'm not prepared at all.
教练让我上来讲话
I feel very honored...
我感到很荣幸 可是
...that coach asked me to do this, but...
同时也感到很内疚 因为我已经很久没来看望他了
I also feel terrible because I haven't seen the coach in so long.
他一直希望我能来这里见见他
And he always wanted me to come to town and see him...
但我总是忙于自己的事 抽不开身 我感到很后悔
...and I got caught up in what I've been doing and I regret it.
我知道1978年的St. Mark队
I understand that the St. Mark's team of 1978...
是教练的唯一一支冠军队
...was the only championship team that the coach ever had...
就我们当时的资质而言
...and that's very impressive, I gotta say...
确实令人印象深刻
...judging from the talent we had to offer.
信不信由你们
I mean, believe it or not...
1978年Robbie和Marcus比现在还矮
...Robbie and Marcus were actually shorter back in 1978.
但他们掌握了一项你从没学会的技巧
But those guys had a skill you never mastered.
他们懂得传球
They knew how to pass the ball.
看来某人得学学把炸鸡传给别人
Looks like somebody has to learn how to pass the Kentucky Fried Chicken.
开玩笑的
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
我们五个已经过完了生命的大部分
We're saying goodbye to a big part of our lives. All of us.
你影响了在场的每一个人
You affected everybody in this room.
希望我们能有像你一样的人生
And I hope we get to live our lives like you.
在生命的终场铃声响起时 心安无憾
Have no regrets when life's final buzzer sounds.
让我们为他默哀
So let's all bow our heads in silence.
你讲完 就该结束的
They should have just ended it right after you.
这太蠢了
This is insanity.
是的
Yeah.
五块钱赌他会单腿跪下
Five bucks it takes him down on one knee.
好啊
You're on.
别那样
Stop it.
你长不大吗?
Grow up, will you?
噢 看看他
Oh, look at him now.
别这么生气嘛 Robbie
Don't get so mad there, Robbie.
Rob女朋友如何? 我们该为他高兴还是...
So how we feeling about Rob's girl? We're happy for him, or...?
噢 天 那个德国大妈? 她看起来还行
Oh, my God. The St. Pauli Grandma? She seems all right.
她挺可爱的
She's pretty.
有点... 我爱戴假发 的感觉
You know, in a "me in a wig" sort of way.
对 就是
Yeah. Yeah, exactly.
富兰克林绑在风筝上 吸引闪电的那把钥匙
When Ben Franklin was flying that kite and it had the key on it...
就是她家的
...that was to her apartment.
啊 太对了
Oh, that was good, man.
但我不得不说 他看上去是真心的
You know, but I gotta say, he seems like he's in love, you know?
他对他前三任老婆都是真心的
He was in love with the first three wives.
一个骗子 一个暴力妹和一个暴食女
The Cheater, the Beater and the Eater.
他的问题在于每次都 太快陷入爱河而无法自拔
You know, his problem is he's always so overly in love so quick, you know?
然后某天他一发飙就把一切都搅黄了
And then one day he snaps and then it gets ugly in a hurry.
您的咖啡 Feder先生
Coffee, Mr. Feder?
啊 不 不用 我很好
No, no, no. I'm good, I'm good.
我是说 谢谢 你真好 自愿给我端杯咖啡
I mean, thank you. That's cool of you to voluntarily wanna give me coffee.
你自己喝 在教堂里学习时喝掉吧
Just, you drink it, you know, while you're studying inside the church.
但您给我发短信 说要喝咖啡
But you texted me you want coffee.
我是说让你喝咖啡并学习
I texted you that I wanted you to drink the coffee and study.
去教堂里念你的书吧
So study your books in the church.
去吧Rita 没事
Go ahead. All right, Rita.
快餐? 你们吃不吃...
Fast food? You guys eat the fast...?
妈妈我想喝奶
Mommy, I want some milk.
噢 没问题 宝贝儿 来吧 妈妈喂你点
Oh, sure, angel. You come here. I'll give you a little something.
慢点 亲爱的 别这么大口吞
Slow down, honey. Not such big gulps.
待会儿要肚子痛的
You're gonna get a tummy ache.
- 你儿子真可爱 - 嗯
- Your son is so cute. - Yeah.
他多大了?
How old is he?
呃 他... 48个月了
Oh, he's 48 months.
4岁了
That's 4.
是
Yeah.
去年打算断奶的 但他太爱吃了
We meant to stop last year, but he likes it so much...
我们也不忍心拒绝
...and we don't like to say no.
嘿 甜心?
Hey, sweetheart?
请你用叉子吃好么?
Could you use a fork, please?
不行
No.
不 不 不行!
No, no, no!
看来她缺母爱
Looks like she didn't get the memo.
- 嘿 那是我的点 - 嘿 这可是凯迪拉克
- Hey. Let me get that spot. - Hey, gotta respect the Caddy.
真好 把你的小猪存钱罐开来了
It's nice you drove your piggy bank here.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
嗨 Gloria
Hey. Hi, Gloria.
- 看这里 - 来吧
- Look at this. - Come on.
好的
Yeah.
哈 Rob人可爱车也可爱
Hey, Rob's car is an Oompa Loompa too.
- 好的 当心脚下 - 地方还不错 住一晚没问题
- Okay, watch the edge. - It's cute. It'll do for one night.
是吗? 你可以吗?
Yeah? You can handle it?
爸爸 那台机器在干嘛?
Daddy, what is that machine doing?
它在赶蛾子 宝贝
It's getting rid of the moths, honey.
把它们赶到哪儿去?
Where's it taking them?
- 地狱 - Higgins 别这么说
- Hell. - Don't say that, Higgins.
抱歉 不是地狱 是墨西哥
I'm sorry. Not hell, Mexico.
不 是对它们放电
No, it's giving them electricity...
然后那些蛾子就被电睡着了
...so the moths fall asleep electrically.
这是电刑吗?
It's electrocuting them?
- 不 不是 - 可是爸爸 它们会死!
- No, no, no. - But, Daddy, they're dying.
- 是在杀死它们? - 不是
- It's killing them? - No.
爸爸 不
Daddy, no.
不 不 没死
No, no, it's not.
我来证明它没死 好吗?
Okay? Let me adjust it.
它们都没事 我保证
Look, they're all all right, I promise you.
瞧 看看这家伙
See? Look at this guy.
他还没睡醒
He's still sleeping.
老爸 它死了
It's dead, Dad.
噢 一个门廊秋千
A porch swing.
这个周末有事做了
I know what I'm doing this weekend.
现在他死了
Now he's dead.
各位 欢迎回到1978年的湖畔别墅
Welcome back to 1978, everybody. The lake house.
一切都没变 真难以置信
Nothing's changed, it's unbelievable.
我记得没这么大啊
I don't remember this big.
这是我的厨房 就是它了
This is my kitchen. This is it, right now.
噢 够了 别再提厨房了
Oh, please, enough with the kitchen.
什么意思?
Why you so mean?
我们可以这么干
We could've done this.
- 一架风琴 - 噢我的天 瞧这厨房
- An organ. - Oh, my God, look at this kitchen.
- 够了 - 你就不能哄哄我吗?
- That's enough, already. - Could you at least humor me?
这是拓展训练营之类的地方么?
Is this like an Outward Bound thing?
这里很像"迷失"里的场景
I mean, it's like an episode of Lost.
宝贝 别这么锤琴
Hon, you might not wanna bang on that.
我喜欢这么玩
But I like playing it like this.
行了 行了
Okay. Okay.
好了 大家听着 房间怎么分?
So listen, guys, who's getting what room?
实际上我给各位做了张房间表
Actually, I made a map of who gets which room.
我预留了有水垫床的房间
I took the liberty of reserving the room with the waterbed...
给Gloria和我自己
...for Gloria and myself.
你今晚要仰泳式啊
You're gonna do the backstroke tonight.
我今晚也要跟你们一起游泳
I wanna go swimming with you guys tonight.
哦 亲爱的 我的意思 不是真的游泳 而是
Oh, honey, we're not really going swimming. What I meant was...
行了 她不需要知道什么意思
That's okay. She doesn't need to know what you mean.
- 我都不知道你什么意思 - 噢我知道她什么意思
- I don't even know what you mean. - Oh, I know what she meant.
回到选房间的话题来
Anyway, let's get back to the room picking.
Rob 你愿意带我们参观一下么?
Rob, would you like to take us on a tour?
我很愿意带你们四处看看 Gloria只是照顾气氛
I'd love to show you a tour. Gloria was just trying to be cool.
我要离厕所近的房间
I need someplace near a bathroom.
为什么老太婆能去游泳而我不能?
Why does the grandma get to go swimming and I don't?
走吧 走吧
Let's go, let's go.
好嘞 这里是最好的房间
Okay, here's the big daddy.
这房子的主卧
The master bedroom.
这间房得让Lenny住
You know what? Lenny should have that. Lenny should have that.
- 噢 不 不 - 我同意
- Oh, no, no, no. - I agree.
亲爱的 回来 让孩子们用这间房吧
Honey. Honey. Come on, let the kids have it.
让这些孩子们呆在一起 干点孩子们的事 会比较有趣
It's a fun time for the kids to be together and they can do kids' things.
去吧 你们共享这间主卧
Come on, go share it. Share the master bedroom.
孩子们赢了
Kids win.
是的 你也这么想吧?
Yeah. Yeah. Don't you think?
是的
Yeah, okay.
- 酷 - 酷
- Cool. - Cool.
嘿 老爸
Hey, Dad.
电视后面连着的大盒子是什么?
What's the big box attached to the back of the TV?
那是电视的后半部分
That's the rest of the TV.
这里并不都是平板电视 孩子
They didn't always have flat screens there, sport.
哇噢 这可是石器时代的玩意
Wow, that is some Stone Age shiznit.
- 是的 挺古怪 - 我要有暖气的房间
- Yeah, that's wack. - I need a room with heat.
现在是夏天 这里差不多有35度
It's summer. It's like 95 degrees in here.
他又这么说
There he goes again.
我有拇囊炎
I got bunions.
其实我有种膏药 我用玉蜀黍棒和草药自制的
You know, I actually have a poultice I make, using maize and herbs.
说玉米就行了 玉蜀黍棒就是玉米棒
Just say corn. Maize is corn, everybody.
是的 他说玉蜀黍 听起来多神秘
Yeah, he says maize because it sounds more mystical.
我喜欢他的说法 "玉蜀黍棒"
Well, I like the way he said it. "Maize."
- "玉蜀黍棒" - "玉蜀黍棒"
- "Maize." - "Maize."
- 听起来很奇妙 不行吗? - 玉蜀黍 真 棒
- It's fantastic, okay? - It's a-maize-ing.
只要抹在布上 湿润加热
I just spread it on cloth and I moisten and heat it...
直接将它敷在患处
...and then I apply it directly to the affected area.
好吧 我的患处有点大
Okay. Well, my affected area is pretty big.
噢 不
Oh, no.
妈妈 我还真不知道 原来"象人"住在你鞋子里
Mama, I didn't know the Elephant Man lived in your shoe.
霍普金斯主演 主角毁容
如果知道迈克尔・脚丹在这的话
How in the world's anybody supposed to get some sleep...
世上谁还能睡得着?
...knowing they under the same roof as Toe-be Bryant over here?
你的话过分了 娘娘腔
You're stepping over the line, woman.
那只拉布拉多怎么了? 声音像霍金
So, what's with that Labradoodle? It sounds like Stephen Hawking.
Curly他声带被剪了
Curly, he had his vocal cords clipped.
邻居总是抱怨
A neighbor filed a complaint...
所以要么剪掉Curly的声带 要么剪掉它脑袋
...so it was either clip the cords or put Curly down.
错误的选择
Wrong choice.
他是家庭的一份子
Come on, he's part of the family, you know?
要是小偷听见这个准得吓跑
Imagine when a burglar comes over and hears that. He must run in terror.
"哇噢 那只火鸡在房子里干嘛?"
"Wow, what's that turkey doing in the house?"
对了Lamonsoff 你儿子
By the way, Lamonsoff, your son.
怎么还在喝人奶? 都那么大了
What's with the boob thing? Isn't the kid a little old?
他胡子都快出来了 蹭着会痛吧
He'll be rubbing her boob with his beard soon.
他会把奶胡子喝到真胡子上 太不妙了
He's gonna get a milk mustache on a real mustache. That won't look right.
等那孩子10岁的时候骑着自行车
That kid, when he's 10, on his bike...
就把他妈放车筐里 像这样
...the mom's gonna be in the basket, he's gonna be like:
- 快点 - 好 等等 我来打这个
- Come on. - Okay, wait, I got this one.
锯死足疗师 +50分
Chain saw pedicure, 50 points.
为什么他们现在还呆在房里?
Why are they inside right now, anyways?
他们干嘛不出来享受湖景
Why would they not come out here and enjoy the lake...
或者在树林里玩点什么
...or do something in the woods?
我每时每刻都呆在户外
There wasn't a time of day that I wasn't outside.
我们从来不做宅男
You know, we weren't. We were always... We were never in.
上甲板锯人头!
All heads on deck!
看 血飚得到处都是!
Look, there's blood squirting everywhere!
- 不能忍了 - 快锯掉他胳膊
- I can't take it anymore. - Chop his arms off.
噢 瞧他要做老爸了
Oh, he's being a dad. Look at this.
别啊老爸 我正高分领先呢
Dad. Don't, Dad. My high score.
就这样 禁电玩 禁手机 禁短信
That's it. No more video games. No more cell phones. No more texting.
现在开始 你们就在外面玩
Just from now on, while we're here, stay outside and play.
我们该干嘛?
What are we supposed to do?
就像一般孩子那样玩. 快点 开动 Becky在哪儿?
Just play like normal kids. Come on, move it. Where's Becky?
咱们走 带你们去看清教徒被吊死的地方
Let's go. Let me show you how the Pilgrims used to hang.
我们还是孩子的时候 你爸总是教唆我们干最疯狂的事
When we were kids, your dad used to talk us into doing the craziest stuff.
没错
That's right.
是的 我记得有一回咱们把浴帘
Yeah, I remember one time, we got our shower curtains...
装进购物车里 把购物车当船开
...put them in shopping carts and went shopping cart sailing.
等等 你们怎么掌舵?
Wait, how did you steer?
- 没舵 - 那怎么停?
- Well, we didn't. - How'd you stop?
直接撞上去就行了 那才是乐趣所在
You just smashed into something. That was the fun part.
我们还互相射塑料瓶火箭
We used to shoot bottle rockets at each other.
你冲着人家的脸发射 想弄瞎他
You go for the guy's face because you wanna blind him.
噢 那有点过分了 朋友
Okay, no, that's a little much, pal.
我知道 孩子们 忘了我刚说的
No. No, I know. Kids, don't do that.
删除 重启
You know what, erase, reboot.
看 看 做个树屋 我来教你们
Okay. Look, look. Make a tree fort. I'll get you started.
Rob在里面住了一年
Rob lived in one of those for a year.
为什么?
Why?
我爸拿走了我的溜冰鞋
My dad took away my roller skates.
黑暗的童年
Vietnam flashback.
等一下 开玩笑吗
Wait a minute. Are you kidding me?
- 什么? - 什么?
- What? - What?
好极了
Nice.
树上的绳子 你知道那意味着什么
Rope on a tree, baby. You know what that means.
我们要吊死自己?
We get to hang ourselves?
绳子和湖难道没让你 想干点疯狂的事吗?
You see a rope and a lake and that doesn't make you wanna go nuts?
它让我想到 我想...
It makes me... You know what?
快让开 我来教他们
You know what, let me show them.
- 好的 - 好的 伙计
- Yeah. - Yeah, baby.
老兄 站到最高那块石头上
Dude, get up on the top rock.
- 这就对了 - 再往后点 再往后点
- Yeah, you're right. - You gotta back it up, back it up.
去吧 伙计
Go, baby.
现场教学
The class is in session.
谁想看看双翻转?
Who wants to see a double flip?
太高了
Too high.
- 现在放手 - 这是个失误
- Now drop. - This was a mistake.
我不能放手 太害怕了
I can't let go, I'm too scared.
真厉害
That was awesome.
噢 天哪 我的腿断了
Oh, God. Oh, God, my leg's snapped.
噢 上帝啊 骨头刺出来了 快救救我
Oh, my God, the bone's sticking out. I need help.
这是个棍子 你们都上当啦
It's a stick. I got you.
很好
Very good.
爹O 那只鸟受伤了
Daddy, that bird is hurt.
噢 天呐 我去找个鞋盒
Oh, my God. I'll go get a shoebox.
这边
Here you go.
嘿 你真的摔那鸟身上了么?
Hey, did you really land on that bird, man?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我好像听到吱吱和折断的声音 但很可能是别的什么
I did hear a chirp and a crunch-like noise, but that could've been anything.
好吧
Okay.
Keith 坐下 坐下
Keith. Sit down. Sit down.
爸爸 我想坐你旁边
Dad, I wanna sit next to you.
爸爸要和自己的朋友坐
Daddy's gonna be down here with his friends first and then...
Lenny记不记得高中时 我们被放倒以后 半夜来这里
Lenny, remember we used to come here late night after we got wasted?
什么是"放倒"?
What's "wasted"?
问得好 Higgie
Nice one, Higgie.
"放倒"就是...
"Wasted." kids...
就是你摄入过量...
...is something that happens...
...冰激凌的状态
...when you have a hankering for ice cream.
- 我想被放倒 - 我想被彻底放倒
- I wanna get wasted. - I wanna get wasted.
我希望每天都被放倒
I wanna get wasted every day.
我想要被巧克力放倒
I wanna get chocolate wasted.
不 你不必被放倒
No, you don't need to get wasted, it's okay.
好了 简单点下吧
All right, you know what, let me make this easy.
17个汉堡和17份炸薯条 好吗?
Seventeen burgers and 17 fries, okay?
好的 我的够了 你们要什么?
And that'll be just for me. What are you guys having?
Lamonsoff
Lamonsoff.
好好好
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
这是所有人的 记上
That's for everybody. Just put it on that.
- 噢 你不用这样 - 我可不吃汉堡
- Oh, you don't have to do that. - I am not gonna have any hamburgers.
我要一些肉卷 一份卡松尼披萨
I'll take some meat loaf, some calzones...
酱汁要放旁边
...but put the marinara sauce on the side.
还有玉米 带穗的或随便你们
With corn, either on the cob or whatever you got.
- 你是要坐电椅了吗? - 什么?
- Are you going to the electric chair? - What?
他只是在开玩笑 亨利八世
No, he was just kidding, Henry VIII.
她要两份 自己的和迈克尔・脚丹的
She's eating for two: her and Toe-bo Cop.
不过 妈妈 他们有拇囊炎足指环 如果你需要的话
But, Mama, they do have bunion rings if you want some.
很好 Lenny
That was good, Lenny.
要点喝的吗?
How about some drinks?
说了是我请客 别问那么多了好吗?
I said I'm paying, so take it easy with that, okay?
大伙 我开玩笑的 大家自己点
I'm kidding, everybody. I'm kidding. We can drink all we want.
我先开始 我要杯可乐
I'll start it off. I'm gonna have a Coke.
我知道Donna她要雪碧 对吧甜心
And I know Donna, she's gonna want a Sprite, correct, sweetie? And...
显然 Bean喝奶就够了
Bean's good with milk, obviously.
我要小饼干
I want cookies.
小饼干和性感妈咪
Cookies and MILF.
性感妈咪? 噢Higgins 谢谢夸奖
MILF? Oh, Higgins, thank you so much.
放松点好吗? 亲爱的 那东西放好
Take it easy, all right? Hey, tuck it away, sweetie.
我要Voss矿泉水 (矿泉水中的劳斯莱斯)
And I'll take a flat water. Voss.
什么?
What?
没有的话Fiji水也行 (斐济岛天然自流水直接灌装)
You know, Voss. Or Fiji, if you don't have Voss.
行了 随便找个白水吧
Yeah, you know, anything you got's good.
我们有饮用水管的水
We have out of the faucet.
水管里的?
Like, from a hose?
自来水
Tap water.
哪个国家的?
What country's that from?
噢 天 来杯自来水就行了 别再讨论水了
Oh, my God. Just get the water. We're done talking about water. Tap water.
那我去拿Voss来...
I go get the Voss from the b...
坐下Rita 好好读菜单 你马上要考试了
You just sit down, Rita. Just study a menu. The big test is coming.
这里的汉... 堡包... 好... 正
很好
I'm sorry, what now?
抱歉 这是干嘛?
He says they have the best burger in town here.
他说这家的汉堡是城里最好的
是吗? 你什么时候开始学中文了?
Really? Since when did you learn to speak Chinese?
从中国烹饪节目里学的
It's just something I picked up watching a cooking show.
很好 也许你应该 少放点注意力在里面的语言上
That's great. Maybe you should focus a little less on the talking...
多放点注意力在做菜方法上
...and a little more on the cooking.
Burn.
对头
You got told.
对个脚趾头
You got toe.
绝地反击
He comes back.
妈咪 我能尝尝她的奶吗?
Mommy, can I have some of her milk?
他在这儿
There he is.
好莱坞
Joe Hollywood.
这是谁? Dickie Bailey?
Who's that? Dickie Bailey?
噢 天呐
Oh, my God.
嘿 好久不见 过得咋样 伙计
Hey, long time no see. How you doing, man?
知道吗 那场比赛有些误判
You know, that game had some bad calls.
哪场比赛啊?
Now, what game are we talking about? The game?
我们三十年前打的那场吗?
What, when we were kids 30 years ago, that game?
那最后一击?
That last shot?
你脚踩线了 不应该算分的
Your foot was on the line. Shouldn't have counted.
我不知道 记得没那么清楚了
I don't know. I don't remember it quite like that.
你们丑五组合都在?
You got the rest of the Fugly Five over there, huh?
对 是他们 男孩们都在
Yes. Yes. They are. The boys are here.
男孩们?
Boys?
他们似乎不可能再披挂上阵了
They don't look like they can make it up and down the court anymore.
你呢? 也长肥了?
What about you? You put on a few pounds?
跟12岁比吗?
From when I was 12?
确实是
Yes, I think so.
你不懂如何刺激我 对吧?
You don't know how to come at me, do you?
再战一场 敢吗?
Rematch. I dare you.
打篮球? 你这身材不行哦
In basketball? You don't look like you're in the greatest shape either.
比赛谁先睡着倒不错 但...
I could see having a getting-off-the-couch contest, but...
任何时候 任何地点
Anytime, anywhere.
我开玩笑而已 我不想打
I was just kidding. I really don't wanna do that.
下次你来的时候 我会给你的小孩多备些Boss水
Next time you come to town, I'll have plenty of that Boss water for your kid.
- 好吧 - 不能让他渴着了
- All right. - Wouldn't want him to go thirsty.
好吧 但实际上是Voss水 胜利那个V字开头的
All right, well, just for the record, it's Voss water, by the way, with a V.
好吧
Okay.
明天会很伤感 要撒哨音的骨灰了
Gonna be an emotional day tomorrow, spreading the Buzzer's ashes.
噢 我的天
Oh, my God.
教练的遗愿是把他骨灰 分撒在Mclntyre岛上
The coach requested that we scatter his remains on Mclntyre Island.
我准备了一个绝美的纪念仪式
I got a beautiful ceremony planned.
Lenny 你也要去吗? 那你什么时候走?
Lenny, you gonna be able to do that? What time do you leave?
- 你在说啥? - 什么意思 走?
- What are you talking about? - What do you mean, leave?
忘了说 我们要搭明早的飞机离开
I forgot to tell you, fellas. We gotta take off in the morning.
- 你要走? - 你不能走
- You're leaving? - You can't leave.
- 明天有纪念仪式 - Lenny开玩笑的 伙计们
- We got the ceremony tomorrow. - Lenny's just playing, everybody.
不 他没有
No, he's not.
你在开玩笑吧?
Are you joking?
我也想参加 我们都想 但我俩得去米兰
I wanna be there. I mean, we all wanna be there. We gotta go to Milan.
什么 意大利 米兰? 那有什么好的?
Milan, what? Italy? What's in Milan?
超酷 Roxanne的秋季时装秀 在那举办
It's pretty cool. Roxanne's got her fall line coming out.
- 时装周 - 四季酒店住3晚哦
- Fashion week. - Three nights at the Four Seasons.
泳池旁有火腿蛋松饼
Eggs Benedict by the pool...
房里有Play Station 3
...PlayStation 3 in every room...
意大利卫视里还有美胸
...and they show boobies on Italian TV.
我要去意大利
I'm going to Italy.
不 我们都... 我一直没说 我们大家会去意大利...
No, we all... I didn't tell you guys, we're probably gonna go to Italy as a...
谢谢你毁掉了惊喜
Thanks for ruining the surprise.
Lenny 没你在就不完整了
Lenny, it's not gonna be the same without you.
是啊 来吧
Yeah, come on.
Roxanne能让我们今晚过来已经很好了 这可是她的大事
Roxanne was cool enough to let us come tonight. This is a big deal.
Roxanne没你不能去吗? 你可以晚点去找她
Can't Roxanne go without you and you can meet her there?
不行 我们是绝世拍档 形影不离
No, we are a team, me and my lady, and we do everything together.
去年因为米兰 不得不错过Becky的校园话剧
Last year, we had to skip Becky's school play for Milan.
Roxanne
Roxanne.
我想我们可以被放倒了
I thought we were gonna get wasted.
亲爱的 我该怎么办 骗他们吗?
Sweetie. What was I supposed to do, lie to them?
不是因为你的话 而是你的态度
It's not what you said. It's how you said it.
我可不是什么神经质的工作狂妇
I am not some insensitive work-crazy dragon lady.
而我也不会让大家这样觉得
And I'm not gonna let you depict me as one.
所以我们不吃米兰的晚餐了
We are skipping the dinner in Milan...
改在这里撒骨灰
...spreading the ashes...
但周末早上醒了就得走
...and we're leaving first thing Sunday morning.
Lamonsoff 现在才凌晨5点 你可以去杀了那狗吗?
Lamonsoff, it's 5 in the morning. Can you kill the dog now?
我再想想
Thinking about it.
去吧 小鸟来咯 伙计们
Go ahead. Birdy coming through, everybody.
嘿 早上好
Hey, morning.
早上好 放那张桌子上吧
Morning. Take it right over to the table.
在干嘛? 臭死了
How we doing? Something stinks in here.
我和Gloria在给大家做早餐
Gloria and I are making breakfast for everybody.
用脱水器 食物就不会超过46度
Using a dehydrator, which never cooks anything above 115 degrees.
- 这些是煎饼? - 海洋煎饼
- Those are pancakes? - Ocean pancakes.
灰色的 看上去像是砍的象腿
They're gray. They look like you cut them off an elephant's legs.
- 我不吃 - 吃了对你有好处
- I'm not eating that. - It's good for you.
- 这又是什么? - 什么是"什么"?
- What is this? - "What is this?"
疮疤?
A scab?
这是脱水香蕉
It's dehydrated banana.
你把正常香蕉怎么了? 你可以拨了就吃的
What happened to a normal banana? Peel a banana and eat it.
孩子们会喜欢的 很有意思的 没那么糟
The kids'll love it. It's fun, man. It doesn't go bad.
- 把它切薄... - 我明白了
- You slice it thin... - I see what you do.
或许你是对的 这是好东西
Maybe you're right. This is good.
- 这很有意义? - 可以这么说
- Is that what it's meant for? - You could.
好吧 我宁愿被脱水水果打...
Well, I'd rather be hit by dehydrated fruit than processed...
也不要腌制食品
Processed food.
- 我只是开玩笑 - 你觉得可以这么打别人
- I'm just kidding around. - You think you can just slap people.
我没这么想 别这么说 拜托
I don't think that. Don't say that. Come on.
早上好
Morning.
亲爱的 小鸟怎么样了?
Honey, how is the birdy?
这是Christian Louboutin的皮鞋啊 (法国奢侈品)
Those are the Christian Louboutin shoes.
我知道我穿得太过正式了
I know I'm overdressed.
抱歉 我这行头是为米兰准备的 而不是为这个山间小湖
But, sorry, I packed for Milan, not the lake.
橡树果做的
Made from acorns.
兄弟 我不吃这些 有没有正常点的食物 麦片?
So, dude, I'm not eating any of this. You got any normal food? Cereal?
Feder先生 需要我为您做蛋饼吗?
Would you like me to make you egg-white frittata, Mr. Feder?
你在试验课上做这个?
I mean, is that what you're doing in science class now?
做蛋饼?
Making frittatas?
不用了 你可以回你房间试验
No. We're okay. You can go practice that in your room, though.
我知道你马上就有个很重要的考试
I know you got the big test coming.
知道吗 亲爱的 你对Lenny过分了
You know, honey, I think you're overwhelming Lenny.
我有个礼物给你
Here, I got a present for you.
熏猪肉
Bacon.
- 请便 - 熏猪肉
- Knock yourself out. - Bacon.
她买的
She gets it.
她买的 她买的 她买的
She gets it. She gets it. Hey, she gets it.
感谢上帝她买了
Thank God she gets it.
好吧 那么...
All right, so...
嘿 你在干嘛
Hey, what are you doing?
做熏猪肉
Cooking the bacon.
别在这儿弄 那是动物尸体 别靠近素菜
Not in here. That's dead animal flesh. It's not going near the vegan food.
杀人凶手
Murderer.
好吧 我该怎么处理呢 噢 我知道了
Fine. What do I do with it? Oh, I know.
抱歉 伙计 对不起
I'm sorry, buddy. I'm sorry.
Curly 你真丢脸
Curly. Shame on you.
疯狂的狗狗
That crazy dog.
肯定是吃了我剩下的面
Must have got into some of my leftover pasta fasul.
是的 事情就是这样的
Yeah, Mama, I'm sure that's exactly what happened.
就是它放的
It did.
我们也养条狗吧
We should get a dog.
我们应该养头水牛
We should get a water buffalo.
Higgins 你在干嘛?
Higgins, what are you doing?
我在家不穿内裤 在你这还没习惯 抱歉
I don't wear pants at my house, I'm not wearing them in your house. Sorry.
那是男人的屁股?
That was a man's ass?
好嘞
All right.
爽
Yeah.
让我们看看 瞧
Let's see this. Look at that.
就这样 伙计
That's it, buddy.
好嘞 扔石头
Okay, throw the rock.
打水漂
Skim it.
朝树上扔
Throw it at a tree.
朝小湖扔
Throw it at the lake.
朝你弟弟扔
Throw it at your brother.
朝自己的头扔
Hit your head with it.
做点什么吧
Just do something.
拜托
Come on.
你穿成这样干啥? 要和Jiminy Cricket约会吗?
What are you doing dressed like that? You hanging out with Jiminy Cricket?
迪斯尼一卡通人物
我们本该在米兰的 记得吧?
We were supposed to be going to Milan, remember?
所以我才这样
That's what I packed for.
剪成短裤吧
Just cut those into shorts.
- 我们待会儿滚铁环 - 我不干
- We'll play some hoop later. - Pass, dude.
你不想复仇了?
You don't want revenge for the time I whupped you?
那是四年前的事了 老爸
That was four years ago, homey.
我只想飞去米兰 吃新鲜的Gelato (意大利经典冰淇淋)
All I want is to fly to Milan and have some fresh-made gelato.
如果换成是你父亲 他会怎样?
What would your father have done on that one?
那小子会被反手一大嘴巴
That one would've been a backhand to the side of the head...
力道重至耳朵喷血
...and possible bleeding from the ear.
就因为我说Gelato 我老爸会把我撂倒踹下楼
My father would've thrown me down the stairs for using the word gelato.
- 你的新发明 - 对
- You got the new Foreman. - Yeah.
Hilliard想给我吃豆腐葡萄仁
Hilliard was trying to make me some tofu Grape-Nuts in there.
吃这个吧
Try it out.
- 你弄干净了? - 对 我搞干净了
- You cleaned this? - Yeah, I cleaned this thing.
- 拿着 - 十分感谢
- Take it. - Thanks a lot.
对了 Mclntyre岛有点远哦
By the way, Mclntyre Island ain't close.
多吃点 待会儿有的受了
Eat as much as you can, we got a big row ahead of us.
你没完全搞干净
You didn't clean that well.
拜托 伙计 你对我干了什么?
Come on, man. What are you doing to me? Seriously.
你可不想口臭媲美马桶吧?
You don't want your breath to smell like your grandmother's closet?
慢点 等等Robbie
Slow down for Robbie, guys.
你们别干扰我
You're gonna lap me.
真美 能去Mclntyre岛是种荣幸
Beautiful. You gotta respect going to Mclntyre Island.
12岁后就没去过了
Haven't done that since we're 12.
我第一次摸胸就在那
Got my first boob there.
- 我知道 是Tracy Thornhill - Tracy Thorn...
- I know. Tracy Thornhill. - Tracy Thorn...
- 对 - 就是她
- Yes. - Absolutely.
有点飞机场 但我还是很喜欢
A little flat, but I was a fan.
好吧 Higgins 你只能想到小妞?
All right, Higgins. Is that all you think about is chicks?
- 我们有女儿了 - 是你们的想法吧
- We got daughters. - That's all you guys think about.
- 区别是 我可以做些事情 - 不对 好吧 是真的
- Difference is, I can do something. - Not true. All right, that's true.
知道我意淫的是啥吗?
You wanna know what I fantasize about?
棒棒糖
Candy bars.
棒棒糖?
Candy bars?
我上次体检血糖过高 Sally就禁止我吃了
No, I had a bad blood sugar test at my last checkup and Sally cut me off.
你可不是小屁孩 你怎么对付?
You're a grown man, how do you deal with that?
我有私房菜 我又不蠢
Oh, I got my own hidden stash, I'm not stupid.
真的 什么都有
Seriously, I got it all.
有Reese Butterfingers 和 3 Musketeers
I got Reese's, Butterfingers, 3 Musketeers.
第一个在"外星人"中做广告，第二个 用"辛普森一家"做广告，第三个为玛氏出品
我把它们藏在衣服里 放在洗衣篮底
I hide them under my clothes in the bottom of the hamper.
很完美 因为我的湿袜子味 完全压制住了巧克力味
It's great because the smell in my sweat socks mask the chocolate smell.
而你内裤的尿渍 则完全掩盖了巧克力渍
And the looks of your underwear masks the chocolate stains.
嘿嘿嘿 伙计们 我要尿个尿
Hey, hey, hey, hang on, guys. I gotta make a sissy.
- 不不不 - 我得撒个尿
- No, no, no. - I gotta make a sissy.
你已经尿了三次了
You made three already.
肯定是才来的尿吧
It must be just oozing out at this point.
闭嘴 我要集中精神
Shut up, I'm trying to concentrate.
只是尿个尿 又不是高考
It's taking a piss, not the SATs.
这是尿尿 还是拖拉机熄火? 什么声音?
Are you peeing or is a diesel truck turning off? What the hell is that?
大家注意听
Listen to hamper bottom.
他是在发莫尔斯电码
I think he's sending a message in Morse code.
我老了 停
Getting old. Stop.
尿不出了 停
Can't pee. Stop.
气味像榴莲了 停
Reeks like asparagus. Stop.
我就是尿不出了 停
Even though I didn't even have any. Stop.
可喜的是有女孩收到信息了
The good news is these girls are gonna say hi to it.
- 怎么了 女士们? - 嘿 女孩们
- What's up, ladies? - Hey, girls.
- 太恶心了 - 看到了吧?
- That is so gross-looking. - Did you see that?
- 不是所有的都长那样 - 你那家伙有300磅吧
- They don't all look like that, ladies. - You gave that thing 300 pounds...
拜托
Come on.
你做了盘混音磁带吗 Robbie
Sick mix tape you made, Robbie.
- 是的 - 嘿 伙计们 我也带了些东西
- Oh, yeah. - Hey, guys, I brought something too.
- 不会吧 - 就是那篮网
- Get out of here. - It's the net, yeah.
冠军赛的
Championship game.
- 让我看看 - 我觉得教练应该拥有它
- Let me see that. - I thought the coach should have it.
Robbie 把这个套骨灰盒上吧
Robbie, you gotta put this on the urn, buddy.
很好
That's cool.
- "你踩线了" - Bailey
- "Your foot was on the line." - Bailey.
如果教练听到这废话 会怎么说呢?
What do you think the coach would've said if he heard that trash-talking?
如果我们不去把那人灭了 我们就会被教练灭了
He'd kick our ass for not kicking his.
- 对 - 或者用学校的老办法解决
- Yeah. - Or we do it the old-school way.
- 让Eric帮我们灭 - 对 就该这样
- Have Eric beat his ass for us. - I know, we should.
不 我这辈子只剩8次灭人的机会了
No, no, no. I got about eight seconds of fighting, total, left in my life.
我得省着点 以免进了局子被爆...
And I'm saving that in case I get mugged...
或者遇到谁买汉堡时插我队...
...or, you know, someone cuts in front of me at Burger King.
- 这才是我兄弟 - 不能再耽误了 伙计们
- That's my hamper bottom. - We can't delay it anymore, guys.
- 他刚咬了一口鸡块 - 现在开始吗?
- He just bit his chicken. All right. - Are we going? Okay.
开始吧
Let's do it.
我想教练是与我们同在的
You know, I think the coach is here with us.
他肯定很骄傲 能以骨灰的方式与我们同在
I think he's proud to be here with us in ash form.
此时此刻在这岛上 我们曾经躲避父母的伊甸园里
Right here on this island, where we hid from our parents...
现在用来躲避妻儿
...and where we're hiding from our wives and children.
对 都在这里
Yes, we are.
再见了...
Goodbye to you...
...我们的朋友...
...friend...
...我们的领航员...
...wise-advice giver...
...哨音复读机...
...buzzer-noise maker.
Rob 别这样
Rob, come on.
我确实搞砸了我的婚姻
I really messed up my marriages.
所有的
All of them.
是我的错 伙计们
It was my fault, man.
我就是忍不住
I just couldn't hang on.
而我的女儿们
You know, my own daughters...
我甚至都不怎么了解她们
...I don't even hardly know them.
- 教练肯定以我为耻 - 不会的
- The Buzzer would be ashamed of me. - No.
没事的
Come on, now.
你还有很多时间去改善和女儿的关系
You got time to patch things up with your daughters.
回去的时候 给她们电话吧
You just call them when you get back.
实际上 还有20分钟 她们就会到这了
Actually, they're gonna be here in about 20 minutes.
等等 你说什么?
Wait, what?
我先啃个鸡腿
I can use a piece of chicken.
别 别用教练的手
No, not with those hands. Coach hands. All right.
整桶都归你了
Finish the bucket.
实际上 我还是要吃 虽然很恶心 但我饿死了
Actually, I'm still gonna eat it. This is pretty sick, but I'm hungry.
Lamonsoff
Lamonsoff.
把桶扔了吧
Go, old bucket. Drop it.
烂车一辆
Piece of crap car.
什么情况?
What?
嘿 老爸
Hey, Dad.
我?
Me?
什么?
What?
- 这瘪三 - 嘿
- How do you get that... - Hey.
怎么生出她来的?
...from that?
百分之九十五遗传自她妈妈
Ninety-five percent of that's gotta be from the mother.
这是最保守估计
And I am lowballing.
嗨 Jasmine
Hey, Jasmine.
这怎么可能啊?
How is that possible?
噢 猫王的头发插到她鼻子了
Oh, no. The Elvis hairs are going up her nose.
很尴尬啊
She doesn't know what to do.
够体贴
That's sweet.
这是你的车?
Is this your car?
我的老男人借了我这坨狗屎
My old man lent me this turd.
因为他可不在乎我会半路抛锚
Because he doesn't care if I break down in the middle of nowhere...
然后被熊吃掉
...and get eaten by a bear.
你的老男人?
Your old man?
对 我男朋友 57岁
Yeah, my boyfriend. Forty-seven years old.
你知道 我也期盼能喜欢上同龄男生
You know, I wish I liked guys my own age...
但因为没爹 所以更需要父爱
...but I'm just chasing the dad that ran out on me.
爽歪歪啊
Hoochie mama.
啥意思?
What does that mean?
不知道 脱口而出的
I don't know, but it feels right.
我希望那辆车永远修不好
I hope that car never gets fixed.
我也希望
I don't think it will.
我拔掉了火花塞
I took the spark plugs out.
多谢
Nice.
我们全部一直盯着不好吧 至少转下头吧
We're all looking at the same time. Let's at least take shifts.
Lamonsoff 你和我先看树那边
Lamonsoff, you and me look at the tree.
McKenzie 我们先来看看她的丰臀
McKenzie, we're gonna look at her butt for a little bit.
好计划
All right. Good plan.
换
And, shift.
Shift.
换
And shift.
我们在干啥?
What are we doing?
等等 我们都在看树吗?
Wait, are we all looking at the tree right now?
是的 那我们一起看回屁股
Yeah. Let's go back to the ass.
嘿 Jasmine 这是Gloria
Hey, Jasmine. This is Gloria.
Gloria 这是Jasmine
Gloria, this is Jasmine.
嗨
Hi.
噢 Gloria奶奶过来圆场了
Oh, look, here comes Grandma Gloria to the rescue.
让我看看
Let me take a look.
噢 亲爱的
Oh, honey.
密封垫被你动过了
You've blown your gasket.
没啥好看了
No good.
大喜大悲啊
That was rough.
如果他俩修车时都算恶心的话
If you guys thought seeing them at the car was gross...
那你们应该听听他们的仰泳
...you should have heard that waterbed action.
就像两只熊在抢鲑鱼
Sounded like two grizzlies fighting over a salmon.
- 那可是很大的动作啊 - 至少他还能做
- There was a lot happening. - At least he's getting something.
老婆怀孕后我就进了冷宫
I've been shut out since Deanne found out she was pregnant.
- 这是肯定的 - 老婆怀孕时还能做?
- That'll happen. - You have sex when they're pregnant?
- 不会伤害小孩吗? - McKenzie可以
- Does that hurt the baby? - McKenzie can.
宝宝会以为是个手指在摸他
The baby thinks he's getting a Tootsie Roll.
- 很好 - 像士力架
- That's good. - Snickers. Snickers.
还是大点的
A little bigger. A little bigger.
那年Saint Paddy节我交了桃花运 不过对方半梦半醒的
I got lucky on Saint Paddy's Day, but she was half-asleep.
每年3月17日，爱尔兰的节日
说是半梦半醒 其实就是睡着了
And by half-asleep, I mean she was asleep.
对 不省人事了
Yeah, she was out. Yeah.
其实就是让你上
You're allowed to do that.
她才不想醒着呢
She'd rather not be awake.
- 嘿 你那女儿怎么样了? - 别提了
- Hey, how'd it go with the daughter? - Awkward.
或许一个孩子的头20年 要比我想的重要
I guess the first 20 years of a kid's life is more important than I realized.
是啊 总是孩子在付出
Yeah. It's always the kids who pay.
是孩子
Kids pay.
- 是孩子 - 是孩子
- They pay. - They pay.
- 总是他们付出 - 付出了玉蜀黍
- They always pay. - But they pay with maize.
跟你们一起真开心
Was good hanging with you guys.
- 不 不 不 这才开个头呢 - 别扫兴 老兄
- No, no, no. We're catching up. - Come on, man.
我很高兴能把你们的开心 建立在我家的痛苦上
I'm glad my family turmoil can provide entertainment for you guys.
给他打打气 我们以前 是怎么给Robbie打气的?
Let's cheer him up. How did we cheer Robbie up in the old days?
神箭大轮盘?
A little arrow roulette?
- 神箭大轮盘 - 我们真玩过?
- Arrow roulette. - Did we really do that?
曾经最白痴的游戏
Single stupidest thing we ever did.
最疯狂的
It was the craziest.
- 最弱智的 - 最傻X的
- Moronic. - Asinine.
- 好了 各位 - 真不敢相信我们又玩了
- All right, fellas. - I can't believe we're doing this.
我们怎么老让Lenny骗来 玩这些白痴玩意?
How do we always let Lenny talk us into the stupidest stuff?
再说下规矩 圈里坚持最久的赢
Remember, whoever stays in the circle the longest wins.
- 这可不爽 - 看谁在圈里待最久
- I don't like that part. - Whoever stays longest.
好了 伙计们 开始了 一 二 ...
Okay, guys, here we go. And a one. And a two...
干嘛要玩这个?
Why are we doing this?
放
Go.
继续飞
Hold.
- 看不见了 - 上哪了?
- I don't see it. - Where is it?
- 太阳太大看不清 - 我认输
- I lost it in the sun. - I lose.
Curly!
Curly.
哥赢了!
I am the champion.
哥鄙视你们这些小娘们!
I beat all you pansies.
加油 加油 快抬过去
Go, go. Come on, come on, come on. Hurry up.
哦 别动它 别碰它
Oh, you're moving it. You're shaking it.
我腿抽筋了
My hammy.
别管你的腿了 我脚上还插着箭呢
You complaining about your hammy? I got an arrow in my foot.
- 放松 放松 - 冷静些
- Easy, easy. - Stay calm.
怎么了?
What's going on?
- Rob被印第安人射到了 - 对 可没抓到
- Rob got attacked by an Indian. - Yeah, but he got away.
- 什么? - 他被印第安人射到了?
- What? - He got attacked by an Indian?
- 老爸 你怎么了? - Amber 真高兴你来了
- Daddy, what happened? - Amber. I'm glad you got here.
各位 这是我女儿Amber
This is my daughter Amber, everybody.
你还有一个?
You got another one?
- 来 伙计 拍一个 - 不 别拍了 我老婆过来了
- Dude, high five. - No, no high five, my wife's coming.
- 额滴神哪 额滴神哪 - 太血腥了
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God. - God, you made me look at this.
痛死我了
This is killing me.
Bridget 快过来 老爸受伤了
Bridget, come down here. Daddy's hurt.
- 你还有一个? - 对
- You got another one? - Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
- 哦 好吧 - "嘿"
- Oh, okay. - "Hey."
虎父无犬女
DNA.
- 明白了 - 这个是Rob跟他自己生的
- Now I get it. - Rob's her mom and dad.
这个才有道理
Now that makes sense.
闭嘴 脚啊 箭啊 天啊!
Shut up. Foot, arrow, why?
- 我觉得要先插到底再拔出来 - 哦 让我来
- I think we gotta pull it through. - Oh, let me do it.
我想的办法 我先说的
It was my idea, I said it first.
- 你休想独吞 你休想碰他 - 谁都不准碰他
- Don't you hog it. Don't you touch him. - Nobody touch him.
大家都不会有事的
We're gonna be all right here.
只要用玉米棒子熬点膏药 再...
All we need is a poultice with some maize that will draw...
哦 闭嘴
Oh, shut up.
膏药有鸟用啊?
That poultice shit doesn't work.
从来都没用 你脑袋进水了?
It never worked. Are you insane?
给老子擦点酒
Get some alcohol on this bitch.
这东西你可熟了吧
You should know plenty about that.
你可是生在禁酒时期的
You were born during the Prohibition.
他发飙了
And there's the snap.
比我想的要厉害
That was bigger than I thought it was gonna be.
煽下风就爆
Snap, crackle and pop.
异常起源 胰腺 异常...
Abnormal origin. Pancreas. Abnormal...
乱透了 乱透了 我没办法...
Such a mess. Such a mess. I can not...
拜托 Rita公主 你是准备一直坐着 还是过来帮个手?
Excuse me? Princess Rita? Are you gonna help me?
不 Feder先生要我复习迎考
No, Mr. Feder said that I must study for the big final.
迎什么考?
What final?
我还想问你呢 他一直给我书看
You tell me. He just keep handing me books.
书名："解剖与生理学"
别管了 去意大利的变压器装好了吗?
Never mind. Did you pack the adapters for Italy?
在洛杉矶就装好了
Yes, I did in L.A.
很好 擦下手
Great. Just wipe your hands.
帮我把这些文件好好整理下 好吗?
I need you to organize all these papers in here very neatly, okay?
千万别弄乱了
They cannot be ruined.
喂?
Hello.
嗨 我是Roxanne Feder 我想确认一下...
Hi, this is Roxanne Feder. I just wanna make sure...
妈咪 妈咪 掉了 掉了
Mommy. Mommy. It came out. It came out.
等等 我还在打电话呢?
Hold on, I'm on the phone, okay?
我的牙掉了
My tooth. It fell out.
很好 亲爱的
That's great, honey.
放枕头下面 我会往那塞1块钱的
Put it under the pillow and I'll put a dollar in there later.
什么?
What?
Becky 我还在打电话呢 我等下会塞1块钱...
Becky, I'm on the phone. I'll put the dollar under...
怎么是你?
Why would you?
没有牙牙仙子吗?
There's no Tooth Fairy?
真不敢相信我居然会这么说
I can't believe I just did that.
哦 Lenny 你没看见她那张小脸
Oh, Lenny, you should have seen her little face.
我不知道自己是怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with me.
我是说 我那么辛苦 却老是事与愿违
I mean, I try so hard and I can't seem to get anything right.
只是犯个错而已 为人父母难免犯错
You made a mistake. Parents make mistakes.
还记不记得我告诉Greg 小宝宝是从妈咪的屁屁里拉出来的
Remember the time I told Greg that babies come from mommies' poop...
然后他就一直在马桶里找小弟弟
...and he kept looking in the toilet for a baby brother?
- 这可不好笑 - 我只是说说
- That's not funny. - I'm just saying.
能听到吗? 很好
Can you hear me now? Okay.
我只是觉得...
I just feel...
现在呢? 能听到吗?
What about now? Now can you hear me?
我觉得自己毁了她的童年
I feel like I ruined her childhood.
总有一天她会知道的
She was gonna find out eventually.
总有一天 但不是今天
Eventually, but not today.
能听到吗? 这太酷了
Can you hear me now? This is so cool.
- 你还在吗? - 嘿 不是说不准打手机吗?
- Are you there? - Hey, didn't I say no cell phones?
我想我们说好了的
I thought we had a deal.
- 什么? - 怎么了 老爸?
- What? - What's up, Dad?
是纸杯电话?
Are those cup phones?
是啊 Charlotte教我们的 酷吧?
Yeah, Charlotte taught us. Cool, huh?
嘿 来看看Becky的
Hey, check out Becky's.
爸爸 还有电话等我呢
Look, Dad. I have cup waiting.
等下再打给你 我在跟海绵宝宝说话呢
I gotta call you back, I'm on with SpongeBob.
那是火鸡吗?
Was that a turkey?
哟 Andre 听得到吗?
Yo, Andre, can you hear me?
非常清楚 你呢?
Crystal clear. Can you hear me?
哦 听得到
Oh, yeah.
最帅的就是把杯子放Jasmine浴室里
So the best thing about these is we can leave a cup in the shower...
这样明天就能听见她冲澡了
...and listen to Jasmine clean herself tomorrow.
- 什么? - 哦 老天爷!
- What? - Oh, my God!
能借来用下吗?
May I borrow this?
注意了 孩子们
Attention, children.
这里是电话公司
There's been a request from the phone company.
你们能不能马上给大人的房间 都安上纸杯电话?
Would you please install cup phones in every adult bedroom right away?
谢谢 好了 去吧 行动 行动 行动
Thank you. All right. Go. Move it, move it, move it.
我说了 行动 行动
I said, move it. Move it.
对 牙牙仙子一直都是我扮的
Yes, I have always been the Tooth Fairy.
不 Bean妈妈是他们家的牙牙仙子
No, Bean's mommy is the Tooth Fairy for his family.
我只管我们家
I just cover our family.
不 别告诉Bean好吗?
No, do not tell Bean, okay?
Becky 我好爱好爱你的
Becky, I love you so, so, so much, okay?
我很抱歉 亲爱的
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
- 好了 我都快倾家荡产了 - 不 你先挂
- Okay, you're costing me a fortune. - No, you hang up first.
快挂了 电话单子要超支了
Let's go. This is gonna be a high cup bill.
我真喜欢在你箭伤上敷药
It's nice to put maize on your arrow wound.
那是什么鸟状况? Gloria在笑?
What the hell is that? Is that Gloria laughing?
他刚发完飙他们就和好了?
She's still here after he had a snap on her like that?
- 她马上就原谅他了 - 你是我的美人
- She forgave him right away. - You are my special lady.
你是我的独脚玉米"棒"男人
And you are my one-footed maize-covered lover.
好了 睡觉吧
Okay, come on, we gotta go to sleep.
明天还要去米兰是吧? 要飞好久呢
We're going to Milan tomorrow, right? A long flight.
休息吧
Let's get our rest.
谁去把那火鸡宰了
Somebody kill that turkey.
我这是性奋吗?
Is that getting me horny?
没错
Yes.
答应我等我们走了你还喂她
You promise you'll still feed her after we leave?
我答应你
I promise.
妈咪 那是我的奶
Mommy, that's my milk.
Bean 我们要学会分享 哪怕是只鸟鸟
Bean, we have to learn how to share, even with birds.
可他都把你喝干了
But he's going to drink you dry.
扔得好
This is good.
我的蹦了3次
I got it three times.
Donna 你要来试试吗?
Donna, you wanna try?
当然 可我不擅长运动
Sure. But I stink at sports.
没事的 给
That's all right. Here.
- 这样拿 - 这样?
- Hold it like this. - Like this?
手放平再扔出去 然后这石子就有翅膀了
Get down low and throw it, and let the rock do the magic.
- 很好! - 噢 蹦起来了
- Nice. - Oh, I skipped it.
- 扔得好 Donna - 太帅了
- Good job, Donna. - Bravo.
你会打水漂吗 Feder太太?
Do you know how to skip rocks?
你问我? 姐可是高手啊
Are you kidding me? I am the best at this.
拿来 都看好了
Give me that. Now, watch, now.
哦 天啊 宝贝 你没事吧?
Oh, my God, baby, are you okay?
没事 妈妈 没想到你也那么喜欢玩
Yeah, Mom, I'm just glad to see you having some fun.
我这就把你行李放车上去 Feder先生
I'll take your luggage to the car, Mr. Feder.
那不是我的行李 那是你的课本
That's not my luggage, that's textbooks.
我很高兴你能自己搬行李
That's nice of you to take your own stuff down.
你没事的 加油
You're okay. Come on.
得了 伙计 你们这就要走了?
Come on, man. Already? You're leaving?
对 非走不可了
Yes, I gotta go.
要送你们去机场吗?
Do you need any help getting to the airport?
亲爱的 有点小问题
We got a little problem.
怎么了? 出什么事了?
What? What happened?
我不会打水漂了
I forgot how to skip a rock.
我觉得我需要几天复习一下
Now, I think it's gonna take a couple of days to figure it out.
所以...
So...
我们先别走了吧
...I think we better stay.
你没开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding me?
真的吗 妈妈? 我们不走了?
For reals, Mom? We're not leaving?
不走了 没必要去看那些瘦骨嶙峋的 模特穿着我设计的衣服瞎逛
I don't need to see a bunch of starving models walking around in my clothes.
是啊 看什么模特啊? 他们哪会哥这样
Yeah, why would you wanna see models when you can see this?
瞧见没? 在米兰可看不到
See? You couldn't get that in Milan.
你啊你
You.
你今天想干什么? 随便吩咐
What do you wanna do today? Anything.
不知道 你说咧?
I don't know. You tell me.
你12岁时遇到好天气会最想玩什么?
What was your favorite thing to do when you were 12 and it was sunny?
哦 这可不行
Well, I can't do that.
要不... 去水上世界吧
Maybe go to a water park.
那还等什么?
What are we waiting for?
- 真的假的? - 准备好车子出发
- Seriously? - Let's load up the car, people.
真的假的啊?
Are you kidding me?
- 我不脱衣服 - 我也不脱衣服
- I'm not taking my shirt off. - I'm not taking my shirt off either.
都浪费了
You're wasting it.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事
It's all right.
其实味道还不差
It's actually not that bad.
- 今天可是美女秀 - 好吗? 你看好他们
- Ladies' day. - All right? You're in charge.
我要嘘嘘
I have to go number two.
好吧 再憋会 儿子
Okay, hang on, son.
嘿 老爸
Hey, Dad.
嘿 你们去哪了?
Hey. Where you guys been?
我们没带泳衣 Marcus带我们去买了
Well, we didn't bring our swimsuits, so Marcus went to take us to buy some.
是家叫"小坏坏"的店
We got them at a store called Naughty and Nice.
Marcus说就这一家开着
Marcus said it was the only one open.
大夏天就这么一家卖泳衣?
The only place open? For bathing suits? In the summer?
我这件是在"走过路过不错过"买的
We got my bathing suit at Stop and Shop.
这件...我喜欢
Now, that's... I like that one.
去玩旋风滑道喽!
Let's hit the water slide.
旋风滑道!
Water slide.
真是个好日子
What a beautiful day.
- 今天可是美女秀啊 - 说的是啊
- God. It's a girls' day. - I know.
好热啊
It is hot.
哦 伙计
Oh, boy.
- 真要穿泳衣吗? - 哦 这天真热
- Are we really doing bathing suits? - God, it's hot.
得了 姐们 反正又没人认识我们 怕什么?
Come on, girls. We don't know these people. Who cares?
对啊 怕什么? 整个夏天 我都裹着这破布
You're right, who cares? I've been working all summer on this six-pack.
好了
All right.
感觉如何啊?
How do you feel about that?
- BB到前面来 - 来吧 大D 来吧 大D
- Baby got front. - Go, D. Go, D.
该你了 Sally 衣服脱掉
Come on, Sally, it's your turn. Take it off.
哦 不 我觉得有点冷
Oh, no. I have a bit of a chill, actually.
Gloria 那你呢?
Gloria, how about you?
我没泳衣 但我喜欢全光
I don't own a bathing suit. But I like to go nude.
- 不 不 不 - 这里还有小孩呢
- No, no, no. - There's children here.
嘿 有人在打望呢
Hey, somebody likes what he sees.
- 老爸 这队伍稳如泰山啊 - 就是
- Daddy, this line's not even moving. - I know.
- 说的是 - 我要喝妈咪的奶
- I know. - I want Mommy's milk.
我知道你要喝 儿子 可是...
I know you do, son, but...
他要喝妈咪的奶 就给他妈咪的奶啊
He wants mommy's milk. Give him some mommy's milk.
妈咪的奶! 妈咪的奶!
Mommy's milk! Mommy's milk!
不 不 该死
No. No. Damn it.
不准再喝妈了
No more Mommy's milk, okay?
要喝 就喝牛
You want milk, you're drinking regular milk.
- 拿来 小朋友 - 嘿
- Here, kid. - Hey.
别跟老子废话 给你1块钱 快滚
Don't give me any guff right now. Here's a buck. Run along. Run along.
拿着 把盒子里的牛奶喝了
Here. Drink the milk out of the carton.
不知道妈咪让不让我喝
I don't know if Mommy will want me to.
你就只管喝好了 看你老爸怎么喝的 老爸教你喝好不好
All right, just drink it, okay? Just like Daddy does. Let me show you, okay?
好
Okay.
我跟老爸一样了
I'm just like Daddy.
很好
There you go.
不吸人奶了
No more booby milk.
留给我们吸
More for us.
各位姐们 有什么办法让肌肉男先生
So, ladies, how do we get Mr. Banana Hammock...
到我们这来? 我们要好好看看他
...to come over here, where we can get a better look at him?
好吧 这就是母乳喂养的优势之一
Okay. Well, there's two big advantages to breast-feeding...
现在我就来发挥一下
...and I'm gonna put mine to work.
Sally
Sally.
对了 姐们
That's it, girl.
哦 天啊
Oh, my goodness.
- 来个伞管舞 - Sally 额滴神哪
- Work that umbrella pole, baby. - Sally. Oh, my God.
- 哦 鱼要上钩了 - 你真行啊
- Oh, it's definitely working. Yeah. - You're good at that.
- 哦 鱼快上钩了 - 你看他那身材
- Oh, my God, he likes it. - Look at him flex.
不 别停啊
No, continue.
好吧 走后门进 我们不排队了 走
All right, doing the back-door shuffle. Cutting the line. Go.
当心
Don't get hurt.
走 走 走
Go, go, go.
爸爸 我们可以走这里吗?
Dad, are we allowed to go through here?
当然不能 但我们还是照样进
Absolutely not, but we're doing it anyway.
想当年这可是你们无敌老爸找到的
All right, your cool dad found this back in the day.
顺着梯子上去
Go up the ladder.
这里面好黑的 牵好哟
It's dark in there. Maybe you should hold my hand.
我好怕的
I'm scared.
嘿 过来 过来
Hey. Come here, come here.
别给那人渣搭上了 离他远点
Don't fall for that crap. You stay away from him.
你说什么呢? 他不是玻璃吗?
What are you talking about? He's gay, isn't he?
不 他只是像玻璃
No. He just seems gay.
他可是老油条了
He's a genius.
走 走 走
Go, go, go.
好了 下一个是谁?
Alrighty, who's next?
All right, who's next?
是时候了 Charlotte
Now's a good time. Charlotte.
你先上
You're up first.
- 去吧 - 玩得开心 Charlotte
- There you go. - Have fun, Charlotte.
走了 下一个 来
There you go. Who's next? Go.
- 他朝这边来了吗? - 他朝我们过来了
- Is he coming this way? - He's coming towards us right now.
- 现在一切正常 - 没错
- This is good now. - He is.
不管怎么着 别放屁
Whatever you do, don't fart.
嘿 你们好啊 美女 呵!
Hey, what's up, ladies?
都是本地人吗? 呵!
So you're from around these parts, eh?
俺是从Saskatchetoon 那旮哒来的 加拿大人 呵!
Yeah, I'm from Saskatchetoon. That's up in Canada, eh?
美国的美女们 去过Saskatchetoon么? 呵!
You American ladies, you've been out to Saskatchetoon, eh?
死相!
Hoseteasers.
一晃眼纯爷们 一张嘴嫩娘们
Everything was on steroids except for his voice.
走 走 走
Go, go, go.
上 上 上
Out, out, out.
快 快 快
Now, now, now.
下一个
Next.
好了 下一个是谁? 嘿 你们不是刚刚玩过了吗?
All right, who's next? Hey, weren't you guys just here?
没有啊 我想你认错人了
No. I think you have us confused with some other people.
不可能 你们俩可是 我这辈子见过的最正的妞
I don't think so, you're two of the hottest chicks I've ever seen in my life.
- 嘿 - 干嘛?
- Hey. - What?
- 她们可是我女儿 - 是啊
- These are my daughters. - Right.
她 肯定是
Her, definitely.
跟你一样 奇挫无比
Because she's fugly, just like you.
- 嘿 - 下一个
- Hey. - Now, who's next?
爸爸 快点 我要玩海盗速滑
Dad. Come on. Hurry up, I wanna go to Pirate's Plunge.
等一下 亲爱的 我们都会玩的
One second. Yeah, we're going on all the rides. We're doing them all.
我们会很开心的
We'll have fun.
你在尿尿吗？
Are you making a sissy?
不 我没有
No, I'm not.
要知道泳池里有化学试剂 遇到尿会变成蓝色
You know they put a chemical in the pool that turns urine blue.
不 不 不 那是无稽之谈 宝贝 不要相信
No, no, no, that's an old wives' tale, sweetie. That's an old wives' tale.
上帝 你真让我丢脸
Oh, my God. You're humiliating me.
妈妈 妈妈
Mama, Mama.
想照相吗？
Wanna take a picture?
好的 站远一点
All right. A little farther.
远一点
Farther.
再远一点
成功了
Gotcha.
这个我不太会玩 爸爸 有点陡
I don't know about this one, Dad. It's kind of steep.
比我记忆中的是要陡一些
It's a little steeper than I remember.
我们还是去玩别的吧
Okay, let's go on another ride.
- 我也不喜欢 - 走吧 去别处玩
- I don't like it either, yeah. - Come on, we'll get out of here.
小孩子怕了 所以你就有借口了 对吧 Feder?
Good thing the kid chickened out so you don't have to go, right, Feder?
干脆花钱请个人帮你吧 有钱人？
Why don't you hire somebody to do it for you, Mr. Richie Rich?
- 好主意 - Wiley 好吗 伙计？
Good idea. Hey, Wiley, what's up, man?
- 站开点 让我来 - 好样的 儿子
- Step aside. Let me get this on. - All right, son.
拜拜 胆小鬼
Hasta la vista, chicken shiznit.
看看他
Yeah, look at him go.
上啊 孩子
Go, kid.
真好 真漂亮
That was good. That was very nice.
我也想玩玩
All right, now I want some of this.
瞧见没
Look at this. Look at this.
- 瞧见没 - 好小子 上啊
- What happened there? - Attaboy. Way to go, Greggie.
倒着来? 瞧瞧
Backwards, huh? Look at him.
倒着 宝贝
Backwards, baby.
到你了 好莱坞
You're up, Hollywood.
我来? 好吧 我不太会倒着跳
I'm up? All right. I don't know how you follow backwards.
但我有自己的起跳哟
Just pay attention to the dismount, would you?
看样子又是第二名了 Beiley
Looks like second place again, Bailey, huh?
- 听到没？ 第二名 - 第二名
- Hear this guy? Second place. - Second place.
用脚倒挂着跳
Go down there hanging by your feet.
让这些白痴看看
Show these idiots.
用我的脚？
By my feet?
当然了
Yeah.
安全吗？
Is that safe?
担心什么 你是只野兽 你是只野兽
What do you care? You're an animal. You're an animal.
我是只野兽
I'm an animal.
Wiley
Wiley.
- 你怎么不来？ - 我有孩子
- Why don't you do it? - I got kids.
Wiley
Yeah, Wiley.
Wiley Wiley Wiley
Wiley, Wiley, Wiley.
你没必要这样做
Oh, you don't need to do this.
我是只野兽
I'm an animal.
Yeah.
脚 卡 住 鸟
I can't get my foot out.
就像这样 孩子
That's how you do it, boy.
- Becky - 你可以的
- Becky. - You can do this.
- 好的 就这样 - 来击个掌
- Good. There you go. - Give me a five.
Roxanne 你看他 好像完全把我忘了
Roxanne, look at him. It's like he totally forgot about me.
典型的男人
Typical man.
拿走你能给的一切 然后 为了买牛什么的就把你给卖了
They take all you can give and then they trade you in for some cow.
我不知道怎么处理我的奶了
I don't know what I'm supposed to do with these now.
我知道
I do.
看到没 伙计
Now, see that, buddy?
这是老式擦板球 选个地方 瞄准
I did the old bank shot. Bank's open. Pick a spot. Aim for it.
你爸爸就是这样百发百中的
Oh, yeah. Your dad'll go 50 for 50 with these.
真的吗? 因为Wii里 擦板球绝对不行
Really? Because on the Wii, the bank shot never works.
是吗? 那你应该去找他们退钱
Yeah? Well, you should Wii-turn it and get a Wii-fund.
Tim Duncan已经是100胜投手了
Tim Duncan's had about a hundred game winners with that bad boy.
宝贝 看我
Honey, are you watching me?
天啊 帅呆了
Oh, baby, that was hot.
- 过来 我教你 - 过去吧
- Come here, let me show you. - Way to go, baby.
跑 跑 跑 你要做的是
Move it, move it, move it. What you gotta do is...
看到上面那个篮筐了吗? 右上角?
See the box up there? Top right corner of it?
喂
Hello?
集中精力 孩子 别看那些了
Focus, boy, focus. Get off of that.
Lamonsoff 看我这儿
Lamonsoff, focus.
天啊 坏蛋
Oh, my God, what a perv.
色咪咪的一直盯着我
He's totally checking me out.
他不是在... 我不知道
He wasn't... I don't know.
来吧 投篮
All right, come on. Go ahead.
坚持住 保持手向上
Follow through. Keep the hand up.
不会吧?
Are you kidding me?
太崇拜你了
Respect.
换上了普通衣服 依然这么棒
See how good you can be when you wear normal clothes?
- 妈妈 - 宝贝
- Hey, Mama. - Hey, baby.
你怎么不去打篮球?
How come you're not out there playing basketball?
- 你知道我有... - 你有脚趾囊肿 Kurt在哪儿?
- You know I got... - You got bunions. Where's Kurt?
来吧 你害怕了?
Come on, are you scared?
怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
够啦
Stop it.
有人要倒霉了
Somebody's in trouble.
不妙啊
Not looking good.
我做了同样的事
I do the same thing.
好了 每个人的头杯酒我给喝了
All right, I did everybody's first shot for them.
轮到你们喝第二杯了
Now you do the second one.
现在开始
Come on, now.
没人那么喝
No, nobody's doing shots.
孩子都在呢 蠢驴 明天还要早起
We got kids here, dummy. Gotta wake up in the morning.
那我们就拼啤酒 谁要啤酒? 举手
We're gonna biz beers instead. Who's got beers? Check them off.
- 我就喝这一瓶 - 我只喝咖啡
- I'm gonna go with one. - Yeah, I'll stick with coffee.
- 我这儿有很多这个 - 干杯
- I'm having this many. - Cheers.
- 我在哺乳 不能喝酒 - 我今晚只喝泻药
- I'm breast-feeding, I don't drink. - I'm just having Metamucil tonight.
你们都怎么了
What's wrong with you guys?
我们以前在这儿都会玩倒下的
We used to come up here and party, man, and get wasted.
你们真没用
You losers.
别担心 你会长大的 你需要一个对的女孩
Don't worry, you'll grow up one day. You just have to meet the right girl.
我姐姐跟你会是绝配
Oh, my older sister would be perfect for you.
什么?
What?
医生说她瞎了 但她还能看见轮廓
She's legally blind, but she can see shapes.
Roxanne 你是怎么和Lenny认识的？
Anyways, Roxanne, how did you and Lenny meet?
问的好
That's a good question.
这坨废物是怎么 我没恶意...
How did this blob of crap, no offense...
...遇到这位墨西哥辣妹的
...meet this lovely seorita?
他在我的百货公司逛
Oh, he came into the department store where I was working.
我帮了他
I helped him.
他让我试穿一条短裙
He wanted me to try this skirt on.
让人试衣服的老把戏
Oh, the old "try on the skirt" trick.
我知道了 真狡猾
I got you. Very sneaky, sis.
确实是这样的 后来他又让我试胸罩
Yeah, he did trick me. Afterwards he made me try on a bra and...
结果就 "我只是帮帮忙"
Hey, I was just trying to help.
- 确实 - 好吧 我是有点喜欢他
- Exactly. - Okay, okay. I did like him a little.
那天天气很好
It was a good day.
天啊 我的羊水 我的羊水破了
Oh, God! Oh, my water. My water's breaking.
孩子要出来了
The baby's coming!
- 真的吗? - 天啊
- Are you serious? - Oh, yeah.
你真是的
Oh, you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我骗到了你 你 还有你
I got you, I got you, I got you.
你强
All right.
我喜欢玩的
I'm just playing.
我的天 这是
Oh, my God, it's...
你们知道这首歌吗? 最动听的
Do you know this song? Oh, this song's the best.
这首歌我最爱了
This song is the best.
这首歌让我好性奋
Oh, this song gets me so horny.
我也是 但现在又平静了
You know, I was thinking that, but now not so much.
我相信性奋这事
I'd like to claim credit for that.
因为我就是靠这歌上垒的
Because that's all part of my "get some nookie" playlist.
带上女士下舞池 现在就是她
Get the ladies on the dance floor, and I got my lady right here.
来吧 亲爱的
Come on, honey.
- 是个好办法 - 我们来跳舞
- That was a really good move. - Let's do this.
跳舞
Yeah, you guys dance.
- 好久了 - 好长一段时间
- It has been a while. - A long while.
我知道你有多喜欢跳舞
I know how much you love to dance.
我是Shabba Doo的铁杆粉丝
Oh, you know me, I'm a regular Shabba-Doo.
Shabba Doo是美国演员，舞蹈家 Adolfo的舞台名
看看你
Look at you.
多性感的Deanne啊
All sexy. Deanne.
你应该改名叫D昂斯 (碧昂斯...)
You should change your name to Deyonc?
Oh, God.
现在有人觉得我性感了？
Yeah, so now he thinks I'm sexy, huh?
能让我和我的性感老婆 好好跳一曲吗？
Can I just enjoy a dance with my fine-ass wife?
好吧 冲着史上最纯情的歌 好的
Yes. To the whitest song ever. Yes.
史上最纯情的歌
Yes, this is the whitest song I've ever heard.
Lenny 带我们来这儿非常明智啊
You know, Lenny, you were right about bringing us here.
这个地方太特别了
This place is really special.
对吧?
It is, right?
在这儿自由自在 我很喜欢
Nothing's going on here, and I love it.
Roxanne 我在这地儿摆平了25个女孩
Roxanne, I have made out with about 25 different girls in this very spot...
我要你做第26个
...and I want you to be number 26.
只要我是最后一个
As long as I'm the last one.
这我绝对保证
Oh, that's a guarantee.
我也很性奋
I'm horny too.
你在干嘛? 你这个白痴
Hey, what are you doing? You idiot.
Lamonsoff 你也来啦?
Lamonsoff. What are you doing up?
- 跟你说吧 太疯狂了 - 什么?
- I gotta tell you, it was crazy. - What?
Sally 她刚才太主动了
Sally. She just attacked me.
从没有这样过 真是疯了
Like never before. It was insane.
我老婆刚刚也这样
I just did the same thing with my woman.
真的?
Really?
Saskatchetoon在哪儿?
Hey, where's Saskatchetoon?
我不知道
Yeah. I don't know.
- 我是什么? - 一匹母马
- What am I? - A hoseteaser.
- 你从那里来? - Saskatchetoon
- And where are you from? - Saskatchetoon.
看看这个
Look at this.
- 我是什么? - 一匹母马
- And what am I? - A hoseteaser.
- 你从那里来? - Saskatchetoon
- And where are you from? - Saskatchetoon.
我们怎么处理Higgins?
What are we gonna do with Higgins?
你知道吗 他真让我来气
Yeah, and you know what? This is what pisses me off:
他不能单身烂醉在这 不用负任何责
You can't be passed-out drunk, single, with no responsibility and not pay.
他应该为此受点损失
You have to be hurt for that.
没错
Yeah.
亲爱的?
Sweetheart?
你又在沙发上睡着了
You fell asleep on the couch again.
你应该回房睡
You know you supposed to go to your room.
你真坏
You're bad.
不
No.
Marcus 这只鸟没事了
Marcus, the bird is all better.
Marcus 他想和你谈谈
Marcus. He wants to talk to you.
Marcus 你是游泳池里最棒的救生员
Marcus, you're gonna be the best lifeguard at the whole pool.
屏住呼吸
Hold your breath, honey.
谁啊?
Who's that?
妈妈的男朋友
Oh, it's mommy's boyfriend.
就是他碰你的
The one who touches you.
他哭了 他哭了
He's crying, he's crying.
- 好了 安静 - 妈妈
- All right, quiet. - Hi, Mama.
- 没事了 没事了 - 妈妈？
- All right. It's all right. - Mama?
- 好了 宝贝 没事的 - 妈妈？
- Okay, baby. It's okay, precious. - Mama?
我带你上楼
I'm gonna take you upstairs.
给你换上睡衣 你不能睡在...
Go and put your PJ's on, okay? You can't fall asleep...
你不能睡在这儿的
You can't just sleep anywhere, you know that.
回你房间去
You go to your room.
- 去睡觉 - 回你房间
- Go to sleep. - You go to your room.
- 你在干嘛？ - 过来
- What you doing? - Come here.
这不是壁橱 这是你的房间
This isn't a closet. This is your bedroom.
这也是你的浴室 你可以尿尿
Okay? It's also your bathroom. You can make a pee-pee.
我在尿尿
I'm making a pee-pee.
独立日快乐
Happy Fourth of July, everyone.
小鸟也要独立的 所以为其祈祷吧
It's the birdy's Independence Day too, so keep your fingers crossed, honey.
- 她飞了 - 是的
- She did it, Daddy. - Here we go.
- 再见 小鸟 - 她飞走了
- Bye, birdy. - She's flying.
她想做兽医了 难以置信
She's gonna be a veterinarian. Is this girl incredible or what?
真性感 你在说什么？
That's so sexy. What did you say?
我想她在说
Oh, I think that she said:
米兰
Milan.
知道吗 那些商店里的家伙刚刚吵着
You know, these guys at the store were talking so much smack...
那场篮球赛应该重新打一次
...about this basketball rematch that's supposed to go on.
真高兴我们已经准备好球衣了
Well, I'm glad we're getting these uniforms ready.
不能再喝多了
No more drinkie.
你真的睡在壁橱里了 真醉了?
Did you really sleep in the closet, you drunk?
是的吧
Think so.
不
No.
天啊 Higgins
Oh, God, Higgins.
- 真恶心 - 你个笨蛋
- That's disgusting. - You slob.
我做了个大春梦 虽然只是个金发小美女
Oh, I had the sexiest dream about a little blond girl, though.
那应该只是个梦
I think it was a dream.
- 天啊 - 恶心
- Oh, nice. Classy. - Sick.
如果放些意大利酱 这些鸡蛋沙拉会特别美味
These deviled eggs would really be good if you had some marinara sauce.
Lenny 的电话
Oh, it's Lenny's phone.
喂？
Hello?
好的
All right, here we go.
又是个3
Oh, that's a three.
一 二 三 梯子 梯子
That's one, two, three, ladder. Ladder.
就是这样 有钱人总会更有钱
Oh, that's it. The rich keep getting richer.
好吧 好吧 Schniggly来了
All right. All right. Schniggly is here.
好了 Robbie 告诉他发生了什么事
So, come on, Robbie, tell the man what's going on.
他才不感兴趣
He doesn't care.
- 告诉他 - 告诉他
- Tell him. - What are you talking about? Tell him.
我和Gloria打算要个孩子
Gloria and I are thinking about having a baby.
多好啊
How great is that?
太好了
That's great.
好消息是她不会有更多的妊娠纹了
You know, the good news is she can't get any more stretch marks.
- 那是好事 - 好吧
- Boy, that's a good one. - Come on.
还有个好消息 就是Gloria和孩子可以分享尿布
You know, the good thing also is Gloria and the kid can share diapers.
这话真难听
Man. You see, that's just ugly.
他不懂 他又没结婚
He doesn't get it. He's not in a committed relationship.
他不会明白的 因为他安定不下来
He can't, because he can't stay in a committed relationship.
瞧 他生气了 因为跟我约会的女孩
Oh, look. He's just mad because all the girls I go out with...
都比他老婆年轻70到80岁
...are 70 to 80 years younger than his wife.
还停不下来了
Can't stop.
我的上一个 金发 高挑 性感 不是你喜欢的那种
The last one I was with, she's blond, she's tall, super hot. Not your type.
我和金发美眉正起劲 一起晃床
Me and blondie, we start going at it and we're shaking the bed...
晃床? 什么意思?
Shaking the bed? What does shaking the bed mean?
我不懂 我只懂湿床
I don't know, I just know wetting the bed. I don't know...
然后就进正题了
And then, right at the "good part." you know?
结果墙上挂的画掉了下来
This picture behind, right on the wall, falls and goes:
砸到她的额头上
Hits her on the forehead.
伤到头了
She cut her head.
破了条口 但我没有停
It cuts her. I didn't slow down.
我扔给她两片阿司匹林 她像接飞盘的狗一样叼住
I just throw her two aspirins, she yaps on them like a Frisbee dog.
好累啊 Marcus 你的鼾声让我一夜未眠
I am tired. Marcus, your snoring kept me up all night long.
你死定了 回来
You're a dead man. Get back here.
回来 那可是我女儿 亏我当你是朋友
Come back here. That's my baby girl. I thought you were my friend.
走开 回去喝你的玉蜀黍
Leave me alone. Drink your maize.
你这次死定了
You're gonna pay this time.
混蛋 让你好看
You bastard. I'll show you how to be nice.
- 臭乌龟 - 你个恶棍
- Bad turtles. - You evil pig.
- Robbie 等等 - 你个疯子
- Robbie, wait. - He's psycho.
停 停
Stop. Stop.
滚开
Hey, break it up, man. Jeez, guys.
- 好的 - 冷静
- All right. - Calm down.
哥们 怎么了
Buddy. Buddy. What's the problem?
这下好了 箭脚
Oh, yeah. Arrow foot.
- 搞什么 - 你们干嘛打架？
- Come here, baby. - Come on. Why are you fighting?
很高兴又看到侏儒摔跤了
Good to see midget wrestling again.
你怎么可以这样? 她可是我女儿
How could you do that? That's my daughter.
- 怎样了? - 和她一起晃床
- Do what? - Shake the bed with her.
你觉得我会这样吗?
You think I would do that to you?
你是我们当中唯一一个会这么做的
Out of any of us you'd be the one to do that.
你连Stimpson的妈妈都睡过
You did sleep with Stimpson's mother.
我根本不认识他 他是你朋友 但我不认识啊
I didn't even know that guy. He was your friend. I barely knew him.
而且是她逼我的 我说过的
She grabbed my wiener, I told you guys.
- 那可是他女儿 不一样 - 我和他?
- That's his daughter. It's different. - Me and him?
好吧 也许我和他调情了 但我只是想引起你的注意
Okay. Maybe I flirted with him, but that was just to get your attention.
- 那打鼾是怎么回事? - 我也听到了
- Well, what about his snoring? - I heard it too.
不 又来了
Oh, no. Twice?
隔着三个房间都能听到
We heard it from three rooms away.
那就不可能了 Marcus不可能找你女儿的
He's off the hook. You know Marcus wouldn't be with your daughter.
我的意思是 不是说她... 你懂的
I mean, not that she's... You know what I'm saying.
- 你头怎么了 - 我换睡衣时
- Well, what happened to your head? - When I was changing into my PJs...
感觉有变态在窗外偷看
...I got the feeling that some perv was looking through my window...
我过去关窗户时 不小心失足撞了头
...so I went to go close the shade and I tripped and hit my head.
兄弟 那可是你女儿
Yeah, dude, that's your daughter.
我压根没和她在一起 你可是我的好哥们
I'd never be with her. You're my best friend, man.
Jasmine也不会和我在一起的 因为是我
And Jasmine'd never be with me, because I'm me.
看 我没有像Lenny那样 跟着谁一辈子
Look, sorry I don't have my whole life together, like Lenny.
噢 Lenny跟着谁一辈子
Oh, together, like Lenny.
拜托
Please.
我接了你的电话
I answered your phone, hipcrita.
是你的助理
It was your assistant.
我问他能否取消去米兰的航班 他说他已经取消了
I asked him if he canceled the flight to Milan. He said he did.
而且是在我们来之前!
Before we even came here.
他这么说的？他怎么能这么说？ 我是说...
He said that? Why would he say that? I mean...
所以是他骗人了?
So he just made that up, huh?
我可没说他骗人
I'm not saying he made it up.
大概是他臆想出来的
I'm think... In his head he believes it's true.
别想忽悠我 Lenny
Don't you agent me, Lenny.
学会尊重别人
Stop trying to handle everybody and everything...
别总是对别人指手画脚好吗?
...and start taking a little responsibility for once.
我承担责任好吗? 你是对的
I'll take responsibility. Okay? You're right.
我觉得与其去米兰
I thought it would be better for our family to be here with normal people...
还不如和正常人一起待在这
...instead of going to Milan.
我们很正常?
We're normal?
我不敢告诉你 藏着掖着比较容易
I was scared to tell you. It was easier for me to keep it a secret.
任何婚姻都藏着秘密
You peel back any marriage, there are secrets.
我的秘密就是 我爱你至深
Mine is I love you. I love you very much.
Roxanne  我只想说
Roxanne, I just... I...
孩子们 任性 骄纵惯了
Our kids are becoming nutty, snotty, spoiled...
- 我们还请了保姆 - 她果然是保姆
- We got a nanny, we got... - So she is a nanny.
不不  她并不是保姆
No, no, no. She's not a nanny.
她就是个保姆
Of course she's a nanny.
啥时才能诚实点?
When does the lying stop?
等这事儿办完
It stops right after this.
她更是个互惠生 不是简单的保姆
She's more of an au pair. Not a nanny.
Lenny
Lenny.
好 好 自此以后 诚恳待人
All right. That's it. The lying stops now.
我发誓再也不骗你了
I won't lie to you ever again. I swear to God.
我爱你
I love you.
是男人就会说谎
Men lie.
狗改不了吃屎
They can't help themselves.
Kurt也肯定说谎了
Kurt sure as hell lies.
我说什么谎了 脚丹妈妈?
What do I lie about, Toe-J Simpson?
拜托 保姆的事儿吧
Oh, please. The nanny.
保姆怎么了？
What about the nanny?
你跟她有一腿
You have a thing for her.
我可没偷腥! 我可是有妇之夫
I do not have a thing for the nanny. I'm a married man. Period.
可是我的确喜欢和 不会胡言乱语 喋喋不休16:39 2010-10-11的
But did I enjoy a nice conversation with a woman that wasn't going...
女士聊天
..."Where's this?" and "Did you pick up that?" Yeah.
我们可以好好说话的啊
What, you can have nice conversations with me.
你不总是忙吗?
When? You're always working.
一到家就喊累
And when you come home, you're just tired all the time.
懒得看我一下 更不会碰我
You barely even touch me or look at me.
他说话像个老娘们似的
He sounds like an old woman.
正如我所说 Deanne 你应该嫁给Umberto Denunzio
Deanne, you should have married Umberto Denunzio like I told you.
要是我跟了他 现在就该你挺着个大肚皮了 妈妈
And if I had stayed with him you'd be the one that's pregnant now, Mama.
想来如此 甜心
You probably right, sweetheart.
我不狗拿耗子了
I'll just butt out.
不胜感激
Thank you.
也许我确实不够重视你 我道歉
Look, maybe I do take you for granted, and I'm sorry.
以后 每周四晚我们都 出去甜蜜一下如何?
How's about I take you out every Thursday night for date night.
周四要播"实习医生格蕾" 其他晚上都可以
No, Thursday's Grey's Anatomy, but any other night would be beautiful.
大家都坦白了 我也不能再隐瞒
And as long as we're all being honest, I think I should be honest too.
我其实不是什么草坪家具店合伙人
I'm actually not a part owner of the lawn furniture store.
我都不在那儿混饭吃了
I don't even work there anymore.
我四月份就卷铺盖了
I got laid off in April.
我租下凯迪拉克
But I rented the Caddy...
扮个大款 就是不想让你们知道
...and I acted like a big shot because I didn't want you guys to know.
Lamonsoff
Lamonsoff.
你没必要瞒着我们啊 我很难过
You don't have to hide anything from us. I'm sorry.
既然大家都敞开心扉
Yeah. Since we're getting things off our chests here...
我也准备坦诚相待
...I got a confession to make.
我戴着假发
I'm wearing a toup.
果然这么蠢
No shit.
我也要坦白
I have a confession to make.
我其实是个男的
I'm really a man.
- 不是吧 - 我就说吧
- No. - I said that.
- 不会吧? - 我开玩笑的
- Are you kidding? - No, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
你们竟然会相信 太伤心了
I'm really a little hurt that so many of you believed it.
- 说说罢了 - 你很有女人味
- We were just saying that... - You're very womanly.
不过 虽然这不是我的地盘
Nevertheless. I know it's not my place, but...
但是长者为尊
Well, after all, I am older than anyone here.
不错 您是长者
Hell, yeah, you are.
这里虽然又吵又闹 但也很有爱
Well, despite the joking and the razzing, I see a lot of love here.
而有了爱 就会有恨
And with love comes hostility.
比如说 Rob那天冲我发飙
Like Rob when he snapped at me the other day.
很吓人的
That was scary.
我虽表面淡定
And you all thought that I was so calm, but inside?
可是内心却在说
Inside I was saying:
Gloria Noonan
"Gloria Noonan...
别骂他青蛙眼反社会小男人
...do not call him a bug-eyed sociopath with a little-man complex.
别数落他的头发像根掏耳屎的棉棒
Do not say that his hair makes him look like a dirty Q-tip."
此言得之
I like that.
或者笑他看起来像一个垂暮的玻璃
"Or that he resembles an elder gay Jonas brother."
够了 他们明白了
They get it. They get the point of where you're going.
或者侏儒矮人什么的... 我都忍住了
"Or a midget Filipino Fonzie." I didn't say those things.
- 正是如此 - 嘿
- That's my favorite one. - Hey.
假发哥
Toupee.
生活充满艰辛
Life can be difficult sometimes.
道路崎岖不平 家庭 孩子...
It gets bumpy, what with family and kids...
并非万事如意
...and things not going exactly like you planned.
可正是因为这样才妙趣横生
But that's what makes it interesting.
生活 首先都是迷恋激情
In life, the first act, always exciting.
接着的才是
The second act...
深度的思考
...that's where the depth comes in.
你怎么不告诉我们 她如此有深度
Why didn't you ever tell us that she gets it?
对 你瞒着我们呢
Yeah, you were holding out.
我一直在努力告诉你们
That's what I've been trying to tell you guys.
棒极了 宝贝 棒极了
That was beautiful, honey. That was beautiful.
一起拥抱吧
Group hug.
好了 就在这
Okay, it's in position.
我不知道 秀逗了吧
I don't know, man. This thing looks crazy.
很好玩的! 我用了一早上才把它吹好
It'll be fun. I spent all morning blowing that thing up.
你应该会没事的
You should be all right.
- 应该? - 嗯
- Should be? - Yeah.
准备好没?
Ready?
跳
Go.
哥还要再爽一下!
Let's do that again.
这不只是小忙 这可是为我投资
It's not a favor. It's like a great investment for me, man.
汽车美容中心
A car detailing center.
周围仅此一家 肯定财源广进
And there's none around, it's gonna be a goldmine.
我不想要你的钱
I don't wanna take your money.
- 你在帮我赚钱 - 我也加入 行不？
- You're making me more. - I want in, okay?
我认识凯尔特人队的老板 我能拿下他
I know the owner of the Celtics. And I can get us that account.
那些家伙可都是开宾利和法拉利的
Those guys all drive Bentleys and Ferraris.
你怎么认识凯尔特人的老板的?
How do you know the owner of the Celtics?
我是他女儿所在童子军的掌门人
Hey, I'm the leader of his daughter's Girl Scout troop.
如果他关心女儿的Cookie Biz奖章
If he wants to make sure she gets her Cookie Biz badge...
他就会跟我签单的
...he will give us that account.
- 我爱你们 - 不错 不错
- I love you guys. - I love it. I love it.
准备好找乐子了吗？
You ready to have some fun?
来吧
Yeah. Hit it.
没事
Okay.
来啊  来啊  你肯定会爽翻!
Go. Go. You gotta get it in high.
Bailey 你真想这样？
You really wanna do this, Bailey?
我们五个对你们五个
My five against your five.
嘿 看看吧
Oh, boy, look at this.
身材保持得不错啊?
I see the boys stayed in shape, huh?
Robideaux 见到你真高兴
Robideaux, good to see you.
Lenny
Lenny.
你在看我吗? 我不知道呢
If you're looking at me, I don't know.
我们只想吃点西瓜 放松下 算了吧
Look, we just wanna eat watermelon and relax, if you're all right with that.
不能算 你这次躲不掉的 Feder
Oh, no. It's not all right. You're not gonna weasel out of this one, Feder.
Wiley都特意逃出来看你出洋相了
Wiley snuck out of intensive care to see you finally get some justice.
嘿 准备好屁滚尿流吧 Feder
Yo. You best be getting to balling, Feder.
嘿 Wiley 你的篮投进了吗?
Oh, hey, Wiley. Was the field goal good?
得了 这玩笑我可是头一回听到
Yeah. First time I ever heard that one.
啊 对不住
Okay. Sorry, man.
要我从天花板上取东西吗? 这个我倒是经常听到
Do you want me to get something off the top shelf? Heard that one a lot too.
说真的 Dickei 我是来和家人 放松的
Seriously, Dickie, let us just hang out with our families. We wanna relax.
怕了吧 我看你是怕了
Yeah. They're afraid of us. That's what it is.
怕球还没开始打 就被你们先吃了
We're afraid you might eat the ball before we even start the game.
Higgins 没变啊 就嘴皮子厉害 但他不能...
Same old Higgins. He can talk the talk but he can't...
后面是什么来着
I forget the rest.
Rob瘸了 你打不了球的 对吗?
We got Rob here with the bad foot. You can't do it, right, buddy?
要是教练在这儿 他肯定会让我试试
I think if the Buzzer was here, he'd want me to try.
他会让我们都上的
I think he'd want us all to try.
这是小马哥吗?
Was that William Shatner?
- 成 谁怕谁 - 大战在即!
- All right, let's do this, then. - It's on.
21分胜
Game to 21.
嘿嘿 一起啊
Hey, hey. Okay, come on.
大家快看!
Guys! Look!
呵呵 这不是在这长大的黑小二嘛
Well, well, well, if it isn't the other black guy who grew up here.
呵呵 我可是这的黑老大 你才是小二
No, no, no. In this town, I'm the black guy and you're the other black guy.
呵呵 我才是黑老大
No, man, in this town, I'm the black guy.
如果我进小白的店子 他们会吓得六神无主
White people see me coming in their store, they get scared.
如果我进店子 他们会魂飞魄散
Yeah? When white people see me coming into their store, they run.
这些是我的小白 找你自己的去
Yeah, yeah. These my white people. Go get your own.
你秀逗了吧
You crazy, man.
运气罢了
Lucky shot.
守住 守住 守住
Defense, defense, defense.
咄咄逼人!
In your face.
伙计们 按78年那次打
Hey, guys. Motion '78.
传给我
To me, man.
有什么大招快亮出来啊
Show me what you got. Say what?
Y哥 M姐 C妹 和 A弟哪儿去了?
Hey, Y! Where's M-C-A?
YCMA为基督教青年会简写
什么情况 猫头鹰在做爱?
What the hell is that? Sounds like owls having sex.
Robideaux 小心!
Robideaux, heads up.
- 你在干嘛? - 承让了哈
- What are you doing? - I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Did that go in?
你弄撒了我的啤酒!
You made me spill my freaking beer.
亲爱的 为什么你总爱抱怨?
Honey, why does everything always have to be about you?
你为什么总惹我抱怨?
Why do you always have to be such a dink?
接球 接球 对了
Get that. Yeah, yeah, right there.
跑不动了
I can't do this anymore.
胸闷气喘的
I can't even breathe.
第二节我腿就麻了
I haven't felt my legs since the second quarter.
你想装受伤吗?
Hey, you wanna fake injuries?
- 好吧 - 好吧
- You got it. - Okay.
- 额滴神 - 额滴仙
- Oh, my... - Oh, God!
我扭了脚 撑不住了
I can't go on. I got a slippery disk.
哦 亲爱的
Oh, hon.
- 我扭了 - 不行了
- Oh, it just slipped out. - I'm done.
有人会心脏病发的
Somebody's gonna have a heart attack.
搞什么飞机?
What are you doing?
完了?
That's it?
Darth Vader 坐下吧
Darth Vader, let's go. Sit down.
加油 亲爱的
Please, honey.
Virgilio的奶油甜卷?
Is that a cannoli from Virgilio's?
新英格兰区一家很地道的 意大利风味小店
你居然和女儿抢东西吃?
Did you seriously just take your daughter's cannoli?
忍不住啊 这可是Virgilio的
It's from Virgilio's. Leave me alone.
别噎着了 爸爸
Don't choke, Daddy.
我们父子对你们父子 如何?
What do you say we bring my son and your son into this?
- 成 - Greggie
- Done. - Greggie.
- 我? - 太好了 上啊
- Me? - Yeah. Go, Greg.
上啊 宝贝儿 你行的
Come on, baby. You can do this.
嘿 Bailey
Hey, Bailey.
给好莱坞的公子准备点喝的吧 比如 Boss水
Somebody fill up that jug with some Boss water, for the Hollywood kid.
是 Voss 胜利的V
It's Voss, with a V.
嘿 能摸下肚皮不? 我很爱宝宝 喜欢被他们踢
Would you mind if I touch your belly? I love babies. I love to feel them kick.
- 好 摸吧 - 谢谢你
- Yeah, go ahead. - Oh, thank you.
这不是孩子 这是孩子的饭
That's not my baby, that's my boob.
- 这货我也喜欢 - 嘿
- Oh, I like to feel those too. - Hey.
没人受伤害的
Hey, no harm done.
- 精神点 - 16比16
- All right, take it out. Come on. - Sixteen to 16.
半场 二对二
Half court, two on two. Let's go.
这回可别踩线了
Keep your feet off the line this time.
平局了 来点真家伙 好球
It's tied score. Tied score. Let's see something. Nice throw.
平局了
Tied score, guys.
好吧 小家伙
All right, son. All right.
- 19比16  我们领先了 - 好吧 孩子 传球给我
- We're up 19-16. Let's go. - All right, son. Give me the ball.
- 加油 儿子 - 没错 Greg 就这么打
- Come on, son. - That's it, Greg. You can do it.
你知道怎么打的
You know what's going on.
好莱坞满天都是三分球!
Oh, yes. It's raining threes on Hollywood.
他脚踩线了 你脚踩线了
His foot was on the line. Your foot was on the line.
可没有什么满天飞的三分球
It ain't raining threes.
- 飞的两分球! - 算了算了 好球
- It's drizzling twos! - That's all right. Good shot.
- 那不是三分 他踩了线 - 再投一个就赢了 加油
- Wasn't no three. Foot was on the line. - Next basket wins. Let's go.
加油
Come on.
就是这样 兄弟
This is it, pal.
干掉他
Take him out, baby.
就是这样 就是这样 干掉他
All right, all right, all right. Take him, baby. Take him.
投了  Lenny
Pop it, Lenny.
爸爸 标准篮板
Bank's open, Dad.
他从没失过手
He never misses that shot.
好莱坞输了
Down goes Hollywood.
等我回洛杉矶练好左手 明年再搞定他们
We'll crush them next year. I'll work on my left when we get back to L.A.
- 这才是我儿子 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- That's my boy. I love you. - I love you too.
你很不错
You're awesome.
- 我们赢了! - 成功了!
- Way to go! - We did it!
嘿 Lenny
Hey, Lenny.
我以为你标准篮板百发百中呢
I thought you never missed a bank shot.
是啊 可是我觉得
Yeah. Well, I just thought...
Bailey家人偶尔需要学会拥有
...the Baileys needed to learn how to win every once in a while...
而Feder家人需要学会放弃
...and Feders needed to learn how to lose.
- 你很体贴 - 是啊
- That was nice. - Yeah?
为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
看看他们
Look at these guys.
- 嘿 Lenny - 嘿 哥们儿
- Lenny. Hey, man. - Yeah, buddy.
我知道你为我们输了球很难过
I know you're bummed about losing the game for us.
你醉了?
And you're drunk?
- 没有 - 好吧
- No. Yes. - Oh, okay.
有件事他们怎么都赢不了
Hey, man, there's one thing they'll never beat us at.
什么事?
What's this?
神箭大轮盘
Arrow roulette, baby.
- 我们都很擅长 - 正是如此
- We are good at that. - Yeah.
- 嘿 大伙儿 - 你要干嘛?
- All right. - What are you doing?
- 最后没跑的就赢 - 别 别 别
- Last one to stay in wins. - No, no, no.
Becky
Becky.
快跑 又来了
Run away. Not again.
滚开
Get out of my way.
谁来帮帮Y哥 扛我走啊
Little help here? Take me with you?
你们真的见死不救?
Seriously, you're gonna leave me?
不要
No.
我们又赢了
We win again.